The days will come to an end.
All things in this world will come to
nothing.
And all things will be born anew.
Remember this, don't forget.
There can be no ambiguity.
Oh, heaven and earth shall pass away,
but God's word shall remain.
God exhorts you once again, do not run in
vain.
Wake up, repent, and salvation is at hand.
God has already appeared amongst you.
And God's voice has arisen.
God's voice has arisen before you.
Each day it confronts you face to face.
And each day it's fresh and new.
You see God and God sees you.
God speaks to you constantly.
And is face to face with you.
Yet you reject Him and don't know Him.
God's sheep can hear His voice.
And yet still you hesitate.
Yet still you hesitate.
Your heart is wax gross.
Your eyes have been blinded by Satan.
And you can't see God's glorious
countenance.
How pitiful you are, how pitiful.
The seven spirits before God's throne Have
been sent to all corners of the earth.
And God will send His messenger To speak
to the churches.
God is righteous and faithful.
He's the God that scrutinizes The deepest
parts of man's heart.
The Holy Spirit speaks to the churches.
All those who have ears should listen.
All those who are living should accept.
Simply eat and drink His words and don't
doubt.
All those who submit and heed His word.
Always see great blessings.
We'll receive great blessings.
All those who seek God's face in earnest
Will surely have new light.
New enlightenment and insights.
All will be fresh and new.
God's words will appear to you at any
time.
And they will open the eyes of your
spirit.
So that you can see all the mysteries Of
the spiritual realm.
And see that the kingdom is all man.
The kingdom is all man.
Enter the refuge.
And all grace and blessings Will be upon
you.
Famine and plague will Not be able to
touch you.
And wolves, serpents, tigers, and leopards
Will be unable to harm you.
You will go and walk with God.
And enter in glory with Him.
Amen.
Hello, brothers and sisters.
Good evening, everyone.
Let's see who's here tonight.
Hello, Sister Tawana, Alberta.
Sister Maureen.
We also have Brother Yanni.
Sister Angela.
Brother Dracos, Warren, Shemaine,
Deborah.
Also, hello, Sister Foilene, Sister
Shannon.
Brother David, Eddie, Clifton,
Deborah, Janet.
Nice to see you tonight, Brother Bert.
We also have Terry.
And a few, a couple brothers and sisters
out there on Instagram.
Hello, everyone.
A big loving welcome, my dear brothers and
sisters.
You see, if you're here tonight,
you made a good choice.
Because tonight is very special.
We're going to spend the next two hours
talking about something that truly matters.
Which will be how to recognize and hear
the voice of the bridegroom.
Pretty exciting, right, brothers and
sisters?
How to hear and recognize the voice of the
bridegroom.
You see, all around us,
we can see that many of the
prophecies about the Lord's
return are already happening.
So the real question is not if he is
coming.
But the real question is, is he already
here?
Hmm, brothers and sisters.
So, I've got a few questions for all of
you.
Are you ready to welcome the Lord?
Are you ready to hear his voice?
Are you ready to read his voice?
New words from the sealed book.
Do you believe you are one of God's sheep
who can recognize God's voice?
Yes?
No?
Maybe so?
Well, if your heart is
even a little curious, then
I encourage you to stay
with me until the very end.
Brothers and sisters, what
we share tonight could
be one of the most
important news of your lifetime.
Alright?
So I will go step by step.
Tonight is going to be information
overload.
A lot.
A lot of information that I'm going to
share with you.
Alright?
So we're going to go step by step.
I know many questions may come up as we go
along.
So I kindly ask that you hold your
questions until the end.
So we can cover everything clearly.
And after the sermon, I will gladly speak
with each of you.
One on one.
And I will answer anything that is in your
heart.
Alright?
So get a water.
Find somewhere comfortable.
Focus your heart.
And let us get ready to receive something
truly meaningful tonight.
Okay?
Amen.
Welcome, Phum.
Welcome, Maria.
Welcome.
So brothers and sisters, thank God.
Let us begin with an opening prayer.
Alright?
Amen.
Dear Heavenly Father, dear God.
We thank you so much for the opportunity
we have to be here tonight.
And we just want to come before you with
hearts that are quiet.
And with sincere faith.
Dear Lord, we have waited for you for many
many many years.
And we truly want to welcome you when you
return.
Dear God.
We know that we are limited.
We don't want to rely on our own ideas or our assumption or tradition, dear God.
Instead, we want your guidance and your truth.
So, please open our hearts today.
Calm our worry and help us to listen carefully.
Dear Lord, we see the world for what it
is.
Many disasters are here.
People are dying, dear God, every single
day.
And the fact that many of
your prophecies have already
been fulfilled, it leaves
us with one question.
Are you already here dear God?
Especially because we know that you come
back in the flesh as the Son of Man.
And we know that not everyone is all going
to know all at the same time.
And the only way we can know is by
focusing on the truth you will express.
So dear God, if you're speaking,
Lord, give us ears to hear.
If you're knocking, give us hearts that
are willing to open the door, dear God.
Lead us to understand your will and help
us to walk the right path.
And we pray for the brothers and sisters
who are not yet here.
Dear God, may you also make a way for them
to be here so that they don't miss the
most important topic of their life,
dear God.
And we just want to place
the brothers and sisters
that are here, put them
in your hands, dear God.
And we place this time of fellowship also
in your hands.
And we ask for your presence and your
guidance.
In Jesus' name, we pray.
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Thanks be to God.
Welcome, everybody.
Welcome.
All right.
So my beloved brothers and sisters,
let's do a quick review here together.
All right.
Based on the couple of few days that we've
got together, we've learned a lot.
We've learned a lot.
And one of the ways
that we learned is also
how the Lord will come
back in the last days.
Does anyone remember?
How will the Lord return in the last days?
Would you say A, he will he will
descend openly on a cloud
because he already became
flesh 2,000 years ago?
Would you say B, he will come in secret in
the form of a spirit?
Or would you say C, he
will first become flesh
and return in secret and then
appear openly on a white cloud?
Or D, I don't remember.
Welcome back, Burr.
Welcome, Ken.
Who remembers, brothers and sisters?
What is the correct answer?
That's right, Yanis.
Good sharing.
Warren and Dracos, very good sharing.
Sister Shannon, also very good sharing.
Sister Maureen and Rosita, very good
sharing.
Alberta, good sharing.
Angela, good sharing.
Tawana, good sharing.
Everybody, good sharing.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
I got a little bit excited there because
everyone got the correct answer.
Amen, Shemaine.
Brothers and sisters, amen.
That's right.
C is the correct answer.
Yes, first God will become flesh as the
Son of Man.
Amen, Brother Clifton.
And then he will appear openly on a white
cloud.
Isn't that right, brothers and sisters?
Absolutely.
So, you know, you know that in the
religious world, right, there are so many
people who are waiting for the Lord to
come back on a white cloud.
People are only looking at one prophecy or
two, and that's it.
And they just automatically
assume, oh,
he's only coming on a
white cloud, and that's it.
The entire religious world, they kind of
ignore.
They ignore Jesus's own prophecies.
They focus more on the prophecy of
prophet, of men, of angels.
But brothers and sisters, remember,
we're waiting for the Lord's return.
We're not waiting for angels.
We're not waiting for prophets.
We're waiting for our Lord and Savior.
And the only way to welcome him is by
focusing on what he said.
So let's read what he says.
Welcome Kisha
Welcome Mitch
Welcome to join us.
You see the Lord Jesus said: But of that day and hour
Knows no man.
Not the angels of heaven nor the son but my Father only. Matthew 24:26
As the lightning comes out of the East and shines even to the West
So shall also the coming of the Son of Man be.
Matthew 24:27
For as the lightniing that lightens out of one part under heaven shines to the other part under heaven
So shall also the Son of Man be in His day.
But first must He suffer many things and be rejected of this generation.
Luke 17:24-25
The Lord also said: behold I stand at the door and knock.
if any man hear my voice and open the door
I will come into him and sup with him and he with me.
And this is one of my favorite Bible
verses.
It's in Revelation 3.20.
Now look, look what Jesus said, brothers and sisters.
the Lord prophesied that he would come back as
the son of man a second time.
And we know that the
son of man actually refers to
someone born of man
and has normal humanity.
Isn't that right, brothers and sisters?
Yeah, absolutely.
Right?
He has a normal process of growth.
He is not supernatural at all.
People can see and touch him.
He lives practically among men.
Living among man.
So when the Lord Jesus prophesied and
mentioned that he's coming back as the son of man
right, or prophesying the son of
man comes, it means that God will become
flesh a second time when he returns in the
last days.
But what is the main work, right?
We know that he's going to become flesh
because everyone shared very well.
The main work that he needs to do, brothers
and sisters, it is the work of judgment.
You see, the Lord also
said, I have yet many things to say to you,
but
you cannot bear them now.
However, when he, the spirit of truth,
has come, he will guide you into all truth,
and he will show you things to
come.
John 16, 12-13 For the time is come that
judgment must begin at the house of God.
1 Peter 4, 17 So clearly, he's not done
speaking.
His main work is to speak.
To speak to do what?
To carry out his work of judgment.
Right? Because judgment is the use of the truth
in order to cleanse, save,
and make a group of overcomers before the great
disasters come to destroy this world.
And we know that once God finishes the
work of judgment, once he cleanses
a group of people who are of one heart and one mind
with him, then his work on earth is done.
Now it's time to appear openly on a white
cloud.
Now it's time to reveal
himself finally,
so that he can reward his chosen
people and punish the wicked.
So anyone who refuses
to accept the Lord's second incarnation
oh,
they will be condemned.
And they will be destroyed.
And at the same time, the prophecies of
the Lord descending on a white cloud,
that's going to be fulfilled.
You know that one.
The one that's in Revelation.
Welcome, Pamela.
The one in Revelation
1-7 that says, Behold,
he comes with clouds, and
every eye shall see him.
And they also which pierced him.
And all kindreds of the earth shall wail
because of him.
Look at that, brothers and sisters.
All those who stubbornly
want to cling to the notion that
God can only
come on a white cloud.
He will never become flesh.
Well, this is what's going to happen.
If you just wait for him to come on a
white cloud and do not accept his second
coming as the Son of Man, well,
guess what?
You will be wailing.
And that's not a good thing, brothers and
sisters.
Wailing is a bad thing.
You're going to be weeping and gnashing
your teeth.
You're going to say, I should have
accepted.
I didn't accept it.
Yeah, it's going to be too late.
You see, brothers and sisters, the
way the Lord comes back is in two ways.
All right?
It happens in two stages.
First, brothers and sisters, it is before
the great disasters.
Where God becomes flesh, perfects a group
of overcomers, that's the salvation stage.
And after the disasters, he openly
descends upon a white cloud as a spiritual
body, rewarding the good and punishing the
wicked.
And that's a punishment stage.
So, when it comes to welcoming
the Lord's return, brothers and sisters.
you've got to
focus on hearing his voice.
That's the salvation stage.
Because why?
He will express more truth.
So, you've got to focus on the truth.
You've got to be a lover of the truth.
Right?
Because if you're not a lover of the
truth, if you're just waiting to see him,
well, God is going to say, I don't know
you.
Right?
Depart from me.
So, welcoming the Lord's return,
brothers and sisters, it's essential
In order for any of us here who truly believe
in God to enter his kingdom.
Alright?
Brothers and sisters, everyone clear so
far?
Everyone clear so far?
Let me know in the group chat,
okay?
Whether we are clear and whether we can
move on.
So, let's begin our wonderful topic.
Brothers and sisters, we know the Lord
will become flesh again.
On the outside, he's going to appear very
ordinary and very normal.
So, in that case, how can we recognize
him?
How can we welcome him?
There's a way.
Jesus told us, My sheep hear my voice.
I know them.
They follow me.
He also said, Behold, I stand at the door
and knock.
If any man hear my voice
and open the door,
I will come into him, will sup
with him, and he with me.
What do these verses show us?
How exactly can we welcome the Lord?
Brothers and sisters, is it by listening
with our ears?
Or is it by looking with our eyes?
What do you think?
How are we going to welcome the Lord?
How are you going to welcome the Lord?
Are you going to use your ears?
Or are you going to use your eyes?
What do you think, brothers and sisters?
Angel says, I'm going to use my ears.
Warren says, ears.
Sophia says, ears.
Draco says ears.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
You're going to use your ears.
Not both, your ears.
Yeah.
Right, brothers and sisters?
You got to use your ears.
These two verses that we literally just
read right now gives us a path.
The Lord gave us a path.
He says my sheep hear My voice.
Behold I stand at the door and if man hear my voice.
He didn't say my sheep will see me.
He didn't say, if any man will see me.
He says, if any man hear my voice.
So, recognizing the Lord means to hear
God's voice.
Also, look at these verses in the book of
Revelation, brothers and sisters.
In the book of Revelation, there's 1,
2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7.
You know what those verses say?
It says, He that has an ear, let him hear
what the Spirit says to the churches.
This is literally scattered in the book of
Revelation, chapter 2 and chapter 3.
It's all around.
Seven times.
He that has an ear, let him hear what the
Spirit says to the churches.
So, this phrase is mentioned multiple,
multiple times, which carries a lot of weight.
It shows that the Lord is going to speak
when he comes back.
Because think about it.
Why does the Lord keep telling us, focus
on hearing God's voice to welcome him?
That's because when
the Lord returns in the last days, we know that he's
going to become flesh.
He knows that not everyone will be able to
physically see him in the flesh.
And that's the thing.
His true believers, they don't need to see
him.
Faith comes by hearing and hearing by the
word of God.
True believers, all
we need to do is pay attention to the truth,
brothers and sisters.
We don't need to see God in the flesh.
Because on the outside, he will look
ordinary.
He will look normal.
Nothing is going to be supernatural about
him.
And quite frankly, we
will not even be able to identify him just by
his outward appearance.
That's why it is crucial.
That when it comes to welcoming the Lord's
return, we've got to hear his voice.
Do not rely on your eyes, brothers and
sisters.
Now, hear my voice.
What exactly does this voice mean?
Brothers and sisters, do you think it is a
physical sound?
Or does it refer to the word spoken by the
Lord?
The truth that he expresses?
Which one is it?
Physical sound?
Or his words?
What would you say, brothers and sisters?
When the Lord says, my sheep hear my
voice.
Physical sound?
Or his words?
Amen, Brother Burke.
Amen, Draco's.
Chauncey.
Shannon.
Alberta.
Rosita.
That's right, Warren.
Brothers and sisters, it is the words that
he speaks.
You see, God's voice is the words that he
speaks.
The truth that he expresses.
You see, brothers and sisters?
It's not referring to his physical sound.
His physical voice.
Like the way you guys can hear my voice
right now.
No.
That's not what it means.
It's the word that he expresses.
Okay?
So, why?
Amen, Brother Clifton.
Why does hearing the truth mean we've
welcomed the Lord?
Right?
Why?
Why does hearing the truth mean we've
welcomed the Lord?
Well, in order to figure that out.
You've got to understand where the truth
comes from.
And where does the truth come from?
In the beginning was the word.
And the word was with God.
And the word was God.
John 1.1.
And the Lord Jesus said, I am the way,
the truth, and the life.
John 14.6.
The truth comes from the world of men.
And yet the truth among men is passed on
by Christ.
It originates from Christ.
That is, from God himself.
And this is not something man is capable
of.
That's right, Brother Burr.
Only God can express the truth,
brothers and sisters.
So the truth only comes from God.
Because he is the source of the truth.
Right?
Only he can express the truth.
We can't.
No angel cannot.
No evil spirit definitely cannot express
the truth either.
Only God can express the truth.
So when God becomes flesh as Christ,
Christ is the embodiment of the truth,
brothers and sisters.
So only Christ can express the truth.
And only Christ is the truth, the way,
and the life.
That's why in order to get to the Father,
you have to go through Christ.
Because he is the truth.
He is the way.
He is the life.
Right?
So welcoming the Lord's
return, it means welcoming
the Son of Man who
can express all truth.
Also, brothers and sisters, when you see
someone who can express the truth,
just know that's the Lord that has come
back.
Alright?
Only God can express the truth.
So when it comes to welcoming the Lord,
you've got to welcome the Son of Man
who can express the truth.
But now think.
Why can't people express the truth,
brothers and sisters?
Why can't you express the truth?
Burke?
Draco?
Warren?
Rosita?
Maureen?
Shannon?
Yanis?
Why can't you guys?
Well, why can't we? Because I'm a human being too.
Why can't we express the truth?
Hmmmm...
Ahh... Draco's!
You hit the nail right on the head,
my brother!
Yes, you did!
Amen, Chauncey!
Amen!
And Welcome, Sister Ebony.
Yes, that's right, Burke.
Draco said, Welcome, Tommy.
Welcome until you join us!
Amen, Brother Warren.
Draco said...
because humans have a sinful nature.
Bert also said, because we are influenced
by Satan.
And they're right.
They're absolutely right.
Maria said, yes.
Yeah, she agrees.
We are corrupted.
That's right, brothers and sisters.
You see, that's why we cannot express the
truth.
So, let's understand what exactly is the
truth, all right?
We are going to listen to a couple of
spiritual, enlightenment words.
And we're going to understand what exactly
is the truth.
Here we go.
God himself is life and the truth,
and his life and truth coexist.
God himself is the truth, and he possesses
all the truths.
God is the source of the truth.
Every positive thing and every truth come
from God.
He can pass judgment on the rightness of
all things and all events.
He can pass judgment on things that have
happened, things that are happening now,
and future things yet unknown to man.
God is the only judge
who can pass judgment on the rightness and
wrongness of all things.
And this means the rightness and wrongness
of all things can only be judged by God.
He knows the criteria for all things.
He can express truths at any time and
place.
God is the embodiment of the truth.
Which means that He Himself is possessed of the essence of the truth.
What exactly is the essence of the embodiment of the truth?
It is the source that provides the truth
The source of governance and soverignty over all things.
And it is also the sole criterion and standard by which all things and all events are judged.
This is the embodiment of the truth.
Amen
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
You see, the truth, it comes from God.
Just like Sister Maria said.
Like Sister Alberta said.
Maureen said.
Yeah, the truth comes from God,
brothers and sisters.
It is what God has.
It is literally who he is.
What he is.
It is the revelation of his disposition.
Right?
And it is what he gives us to be our life.
So only the words God expresses are the
truth.
Every word God expresses in every age is
the truth.
So since God is the essence of the truth,
then everything he says is also the truth.
Why?
Because God is our creator.
He possesses authority and power.
He manages and holds sovereignty over all
things.
So yes, only he can express the truth.
And I want to share with you some
characteristics of God's voice.
Alright?
First of all, God's words have authority
and power.
That's right.
Right?
Because God's words does have authority
and power.
Because every single thing that God
expresses, it shall be accomplished.
Heaven and earth shall pass away,
but the word of God shall never pass away.
Everything that comes from the mouth of
God has authority and power.
Now we, on the other hand, that's a little
bit different.
We have absolutely no authority.
And everything we say just quickly passes
away.
Right?
But let me give you an
example of God's authority and
power from the Old Testament
and from the New Testament.
From the Old Testament.
Right?
Genesis 1-3.
And God said, Let there be light.
And there was light.
Look at that, brothers and sisters.
Here, the moment God spoke, light
appeared.
This shows his words have the authority
and the power to create all things.
And then we have John 11-43.
Jesus cried with a loud voice,
Lazarus, come forth.
And he that was dead came forth.
So, the Lord's words can bring people
life.
Words of corrupt mankind can never do such
thing.
And I think we can all agree.
That's number one.
Number two, God's words reveal his
disposition and what he has and is.
What does that mean?
Because from the word of God, you see
clearly of who God is.
His righteousness, his holiness,
his almightiness, you name it.
From the word of God, you get to know who
God is.
Number three, God's words can expose our
corruption.
That's right, too.
Because the word of God is like a sharp
double-edged sword piercing straight.
To the human heart, right?
So they can expose all the corruption that
is hidden deep inside of our hearts.
Whereas human words, they can't do that,
right?
You can't see into my heart.
I can't see into your heart.
But God can, so only he can expose us.
So only God's words can guide us on the
right path in life.
And now, number four, God's words reveal
mysteries.
Such as how God holds sovereignty over the
universe and all things.
How he holds sovereignty over not only the
material world, but we know that God holds
sovereignty over
the invisible spiritual
realm as well, which
we don't have access to.
And how he determines everyone's outcome
and destination.
Look at that, brothers and sisters.
So speaking of the Lord's return,
I know some brothers and sisters,
you know, probably when we share that the
Lord is going to be become flesh again,
you may feel worried, right?
Because you don't want to be misled by a
false Christ or a false prophet.
But let me tell you something.
A false Christ and a false prophet,
they absolutely cannot express the truth.
Their words have no authority.
They cannot supply us with life, let alone
even save themselves or save any of us.
So when you have a meaningful
understanding that only God is the truth
and only God can express the truth,
that no human, no satanic evil spirit can
express it, then you will be able to
believe that this Son of Man, no matter
how ordinary he appears on the outside,
hey, he is still the embodiment of God.
He is still the embodiment of the truth.
He is still God incarnate.
So this is very important to understand,
okay, brothers and sisters?
Humans, prophets, false Christ, evil
spirits, they cannot express the truth.
Only the true Christ can express the
truth.
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
So far, so clear so far, right?
We're on the same page.
Only our Lord and Savior, our Creator,
can express the truth.
Amen.
Thanks be to God.
So, you know, the other day I had a sister
say, Sister Thelma, right?
How are we going to know then?
If only he can express the truth,
how are we going to know?
It's really God speaking.
How are we going to know it's really Him
speaking?
Well, I share this Bible verse with her.
I said, Sister, look what the Lord Jesus
said in the book of John, chapter 8,
verses 47.
The Lord clearly said, He that is of God
hears God's words.
You therefore hear them not, because you
are not of God.
And I told her, brothers
and sisters, that,
when it comes to hearing the
voice of God, it's not difficult.
People, people think it's really hard to
hear God's voice through His words.
It's not.
I reminded her that, you know,
think of when all of us, you know,
when we first had faith in the Lord Jesus,
right?
How did you feel when you first heard
Jesus' words?
How did you feel?
You see, even though we never had any
experience, right?
But the moment we heard, we felt that it
was the truth.
Isn't that right, brothers and sisters?
You felt that Jesus' words in the Bible
had authority and power.
It was incredibly deep that even until
today we cannot comprehend.
They are mysteries.
Completely unfathomable to us.
You see, that came from our spiritual
inspiration and intuition at work.
So when it comes to
discerning the voice of God.
it means recognizing
God's utterance.
It means recognizing the unique
characteristics of the Creator's speech.
Even in the flesh, God speaks to all of
humanity from the highest place.
This is the tone and the characteristics
of God's voice.
His authority and position are clearly
revealed in His words.
And you could also say, it is the unique
way the Creator speaks.
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
So let's do a little bit of a review.
Alright, let's do a little bit of a review
here.
What are the characteristics of God's
voice that we just went through?
It is the fact that it has authority and
power.
The Word of God has authority and power.
The Word of God can reveal mysteries.
And the Word of God can expose our
corruption and can supply us with life.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Amen.
My dear brothers and
sisters, would you like to hear of two perfect
examples from the Bible?
Two characters in the Bible that actually
recognize the Lord Jesus to be the Messiah.
I'll give you two.
There is the first one.
Can anyone tell me who is this woman in
the picture?
It will come to you very soon,
okay?
Who is this woman in the picture,
brothers and sisters?
She is a prime example of one of the many
who can recognize the voice of God.
Does anyone know who it is?
Amen, Chauncey. Anyone else?
Who is this lady in the photo,
brothers and sisters?
Anybody know?
Anybody know the characters of the Bible?
Oh, Yannis.
Angela knows, maybe.
It's not Mary.
Brothers and sisters, it's the Samaritan
woman.
Yes, that's right.
That's right.
Alberta and Chauncey.
It's the Samaritan woman by the well.
Yeah, look, she's by the well.
The well kind of gave it away.
But nonetheless, 2000
years ago, God became
flesh for the very first
time as the Lord Jesus.
You see, on the outside, he appeared
ordinary.
Look at him.
He looks ordinary, normal.
But do you know how the Samaritan woman
recognized him?
Because let me tell you the story a little
bit.
In the beginning, at first, the Lord Jesus
appeared to her.
And he said, and he asked her for a drink
of water.
And what does she say, brothers and
sisters?
Does she say yes or no?
When he asked her for a drink of water.
Did the Samaritan woman say yes or no?
If anyone knows the story.
What does she say?
Yes or no?
Ronnie says she said yes.
What about others?
She said yes?
Pamela said yes?
Anyone else?
Actually, brothers and sisters,
she said no.
The Samaritan woman actually told the Lord
Jesus no, not yes.
Yeah, I know Sister Pamela.
Yeah, she said no.
She said, I'm a Samaritan and you are a
Jew.
So she said no to him.
Because remember, she obviously did not
know who he was by appearance.
It's not like in his forehead it said,
I am the Messiah.
All she seen was a Jew.
All she seen was a man.
So when he said, pour
me a glass of water,
she said no, I'm a
Samaritan, you're a Jew.
She's seen him as a Jew.
You see, as an ordinary Jew.
But look what the Lord Jesus said to her.
The Lord Jesus said, well, whoever drinks
the water that I shall give him
shall never thirst, but the water that I shall
give sorry, whoever drinks the water that
I shall give him shall never thirst,
but the water that I shall give him shall be in him a well of water springing up to eternal life.
be So clearly, brothers and sisters,
remember, we're trying to compare
Jesus' words to the characteristics of God's
voice, right?
God's voice has authority and power.
It reveals mysteries and it can expose us.
So right here, you can see that's already
the first characteristic.
It has authority and power.
Wow.
She's like, wow, I want that water.
But let me tell you something.
The Lord Jesus, when he said, I have the
water, the well of water that can spring
up to everlasting life, he was not talking
about the water that we drink.
He was talking about his truth,
his words.
Because, you know, Jesus spoke a lot
through parables.
So he was talking about the truth here.
And that's when she said she wanted the
water, right?
She really wanted the water, brothers and
sisters.
So these words carried authority and
power.
And then later, the Lord Jesus exposed
her.
That's another characteristic.
How did he expose her?
Jesus knew how many husbands she had had.
Yeah, because she said, and at that time,
she's like, the woman, she said,
Sir, I perceive that you are a prophet.
So she went from seeing him as an ordinary
Jew to seeing him as a prophet.
Because why?
The Lord Jesus revealed her secret.
And later, the Samaritan
woman asked the Lord Jesus
where people
ought to worship God.
Because she was a Samaritan.
She actually was not allowed in the
synagogues, in the temples.
She wasn't allowed, brothers and sisters.
So she asked the Lord Jesus, well,
where shall we worship God?
Right?
And look what the Lord Jesus said.
The Lord Jesus said, God is a spirit.
And he...
And they that worship him must worship him
in spirit and in truth.
Look at that brothers and sisters.
Just with one sentence, Jesus was able to
resolve her confusion.
No one else could do that.
He didn't need to open the Bible.
He didn't need to open a book.
He can just express the truth because he's
God incarnate.
And that's when the Samaritan woman
finally recognized the Lord Jesus.
And she said, I know the Messiah comes,
which is called Christ.
When he has come, he will tell us these
things.
So from that process, brothers and
sisters, the Samaritan woman,
she didn't rely on her eyes to welcome the Lord
Jesus.
No, instead, she recognized him by
listening carefully to his words.
As we should all do.
That's one example.
Now we have another example, brothers and
sisters.
Now who can tell me who this is in the,
in this picture, just one more example,
who's this in this picture,
that's another character
that, uh, recognize the
Lord Jesus to be the Messiah.
Does anyone know who this is?
I'll take the first answer of who can
guess who is that?
The first one was the Samaritan woman.
The second one is the fish brother.
It's Peter.
That's right.
Clifton.
Amen.
Chauncey and Maureen that's Peter, not
the fish brother Jay goes, that's funny.
Yes, it's Peter brothers and sisters.
All right.
So at that time, did you know that Peter
was a true, true believer because Jesus
asked the disciples, will you also go
away?
Because why many people at that time were
condemning the Lord Jesus.
So he said, are you going to go away and
look what Simon Peter answered,
Lord, Lord, to whom shall we go?
You have the words of eternal life.
So basically he said, I'm
not going anywhere because
you have the words that
can give me eternal life.
So from this, we could see Peter also
confirmed the Lord, Jesus's identity and
his essence by listening to the word of
the Lord Jesus.
Right?
So to recognize the Lord,
brothers and sisters, you
obviously cannot rely on
your eyes to remember corrupt.
Mankind's eyes is very, very corrupted,
right?
We can be deceived by what
we see, but not by what we
hear because the truth
never lies brothers and sisters.
That's why it's so important to focus on
hearing God's voice.
As long as he can express the
truth, no matter how ordinary
or normal he may appear
on the outside, he is still Christ.
So to recognize the Lord, don't use your
eyes, use your ears.
All right.
Use your ears, brothers and sisters.
That's why the Lord Jesus.
Did say upon his second coming,
he will express more truth.
He literally said, I
have yet many things
to say to you, but you
cannot bear them now.
However, when he, the
spirit of truth has come, he will
guide you into all truth and
he will show you things to come.
John 16, 12 to 13.
You see these many things, it shows us,
right?
That he will still guide us into all
truth.
Brothers and sisters, the Lord has never
spoken these truths before.
No one has ever heard these truths before.
There are obviously
truths that are not recorded
in the Bible and God
will speak in the last days.
All right.
So when he comes back, does anyone
remember when the Lord returns?
Do you think he will speak words that are
already recorded in the Bible or will he
express new words outside of the Bible
that he has never spoken before?
A.
The Bible only records what the Lord Jesus
said in the past.
When the Lord returns in the
last days, he will express new words outside of the Bible
that he has never spoken before.
Or B.
He's going to repeat the words in the
Bible.
Or C.
You don't remember.
What do you think, brothers and sisters?
Amen.
Amen, Draco's.
Amen, Warren.
Amen, Pamela, Alberta, Maureen,
Burt, Shemaine.
Amen, Deborah.
My dear sister, Shannon, and Cliff.
Very close, Maria.
Very close.
Brother Yannis, do you want to give Sister
Maria the correct answer?
Oh yeah, Ronnie and Maria were not here
yesterday.
That's why.
Amen, Sister Angela.
Yeah, Ronnie and Maria were not here on
the second day and the third day,
so maybe that's why.
But yes, the correct answer is A.
Alright, A is the correct answer.
So, my dear brothers and sisters,
if there is a son of man who,
one, can open the sealed book, who,
two, can do the work of judgment,
and who, three, can
cleanse and save us,
just know that is the Lord
that has come back.
Alright?
Now, I want to ask you another question.
Brothers and sisters, you know,
in the Bible, especially in Matthew 25, 5.
it says, And at midnight there was a
cry made, Behold, the bridegroom comes,
go you out to meet him.
Brothers and sisters, if you were to hear
me loudly testify that the Lord Jesus has
actually already returned in the flesh to
express the truth, how would you react?
I want to know.
If I were to tell you, brothers and
sisters, guess what?
The Lord has actually already come back.
He's here on earth.
The son of man is here.
He's expressing the truth.
How would you react?
Would you say, A, this is the most
important thing in my life.
I'm going to investigate.
I'm going to listen carefully
because I don't want
to be a foolish virgin who
misses the Lord's return.
Or would you say, B, I'm not going to
listen.
I won't even believe it either.
Take me out of this fellowship.
Or C, I'm not too sure.
Never thought about it.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Amen.
Thanks be to God.
I could see you guys
are a wise virgin because
I would say the same
thing you guys are saying.
And I was in the same position all of you
are in right now about six years ago.
All right?
Now I can finally tell you.
So brothers and sisters, you know,
how do you feel, right?
Do you feel that like over
the past few days,
you've been learning so many truth that
you've never heard before?
What do you think?
You feel like you've been learning a lot?
Every day you've been learning,
right?
I know me too, brothers and sisters.
Even though I've been
in this fellowship for six years
every day I'm always
learning something new.
And are you curious where these truth come
from?
You know, that's why I really want to
share this great news with all of you.
So I really hope that from here on end,
everyone is going to listen carefully.
I hope you're ready.
All right, brothers and sisters.
So my dear brothers and sisters,
the reason why I asked you that question
earlier, it's because the Lord really has
already come back.
Yeah.
You see many prophecies of the Lord's
return has already been fulfilled.
It's not the fact that he's fulfilling
them in heaven.
No, he's fulfilling them here,
right here on earth, brothers and sisters.
You see the son of man who've been,
we have been waiting for day and night.
He's already here.
He's expressing many, many, many truth
already.
And after, after reading these
words, you know, so many
people believe it is the
voice of God, myself included.
Many people are certain
that this son of man who
expresses all the truth is
actually the return Lord Jesus.
He is almighty God.
And yes, almighty God has already
expressed all the truth in order to
cleanse us and to save us.
He has revealed the
mysteries of God's 6,000 year management plan that we
actually talked about last night.
Yeah.
And also the work of judgment has already
begun for the believers.
And brothers and sisters, we are now in
the age of kingdom.
Remember, we are in the training of the
kingdom.
We are no longer in the grace period.
We are now in the training of the kingdom,
brothers and sisters.
So yes, what I wanted to share with you
all is the Lord Jesus has returned in the flesh.
and has
expressed all the truth.
Brothers and sisters, how do you feel?
Are you shocked?
Are you excited?
Are you like, oh no, this is too much.
How does it make you
feel when I,
when I share with you that the Lord
has already come back?
Yeah.
How does it make you feel?
And be honest too.
Okay.
Be honest.
Brother Warren said it's about time.
Brother Warren, this is exactly what I
said too.
Brothers and sisters, for me during COVID,
that was the time for me actually.
I don't know.
I felt the sense of urgency in my heart
when COVID happened.
I shared that a little bit in my story on
my profile.
During COVID, I just felt like the world
was in shambles.
I don't know.
I just felt like a sense of urgency in my
heart to seek the truth.
And I did.
I listened to the spirit in my heart.
And I did, brothers and sisters.
Brothers and sisters, and I came across
this amazing online sermon.
And I'm glad that I did because it changed
my life.
I've been here for six years now.
I get to eat and drink the word of God
with many believers all over the world.
It's one of the greatest
feelings brothers and sisters,
you know, I come to really learn
that your family is God's family.
That's the family that you'll enter the
kingdom of heaven.
It's an eternal family.
You know, because like when you look around,
how many people really seek the truth?
How many of your family seek the truth?
How many of your family like to talk about
God?
How many of your family like to expose
their corruption so that they can change?
Not really.
But when you surround yourself with true
believers, it's it's different.
It's a different feeling brothers and
sisters.
All right.
So I know some of you may feel wow,
this is so sudden.
Or maybe you're thinking this is not the
right time.
But remember, Jesus
actually told us that he would
come back at a time
where we least expect it.
Just as he said, therefore be also ready.
He says you got to be ready.
Because in such an hour as you think not,
the Son of Man comes.
Well, I'm pretty sure you all did not
expect that June 18, 2026 was the day that
you heard the Lord has actually already
been here on earth.
Pretty amazing, isn't it brothers and
sisters?
Because at the end of
the day, we can't decide
when whether when God
comes,
God has the authority to decide.
Instead, what does God asks us to do?
He asks us to open our hearts and to seek
the truth wholeheartedly.
He that seeks shall find.
He that knocks shall be open.
Right?
Because at the end of
the day, God's work is never based on human
notions or human imagination.
Remember, God's thoughts are higher than
man's thoughts.
We cannot completely fathom God's work.
But whatever you do, do not delimit God,
okay?
Do not delimit his work.
Do not oppose him, brothers and sisters.
Do not judge him.
This is the bare minimum, the bare
minimum.
Because whether we can welcome the Lord
really determines our final outcome.
That's okay, Ebony.
That's okay.
The most important thing is to seek.
All right?
The most important thing is to seek,
Ebony.
All right?
So brothers and sisters, how do we confirm
that God has already come?
The only path is to listen.
To the word of God.
So my dear brothers
and sisters, would you like to read Almighty God's
words tonight here with me?
Would all of you like to read God's words
with me here tonight, brothers and sisters?
Yes?
No?
Maybe so?
Sister Ebony, there are mysteries to that.
It's not just about you got to feel him.
Sister, you got to focus on the truth.
You shall know the truth.
My sheep hear my voice.
All right?
So let's listen to his words, my dear
sister.
All right?
So brothers and sisters, I'm going to send
three powerful passages.
All right?
Three powerful passages, brothers and
sisters.
And I'm going to play an audio.
When I play the audio, I want you to read
along because this audio is being read by
brothers and sisters who have already
accepted the Lord's return.
So they recorded this audio for us.
Okay?
So please listen carefully.
And as you listen, you
got to ask yourself, who has
the power and the authority
to express these words?
Let's listen to passage number one.
I was once known as Jehovah.
I was also called the Messiah.
And people once called me Jesus the Savior,
because they loved and respected me.
But today I am not the Jehovah or Jesus
that people knew in times past.
I am the God who has returned in the last
days.
The God who shall bring the age to an end.
I am the God himself that rises up at the
ends of the earth.
Replete with my entire disposition and
full of authority, honor and glory.
People have never engaged
with me, have never known me.
and have always been
ignorant of my disposition.
From the creation of the world until
today, not one person has seen me.
This is the God who appears to man during
the last days, but is hidden among men.
He resides among man, true and real,
like the burning sun and the flaming fire,
filled with power and brimming with
authority.
There is not a single person or thing that
shall not be judged by my words,
and not a single
person or thing that shall
not be purified through
the burning of fire.
Eventually, all nations shall
be blessed because of my
and also smashed to
pieces because of my words.
In this way, all people during the last days
shall see that I am the Savior returned.
I am the Almighty God that conquers all of
mankind.
And I was once the sin offering for man.
But in the last days, I also become the
flames of the sun that burn all things,
as well as the sun of righteousness that
reveals all things.
Such is my work of the last days.
I took this name and am possessed of this
disposition, so that all people may see
that I am a righteous God, and am the
burning sun and the flaming fire.
It is so that all may
worship me, the only true God.
and so that they
may see my true face.
I am not only the God of the Israelites,
and am not just the Redeemer.
I am the God of all creatures throughout
heavens and earth and seas.
Amen.
Now, I am going to send the second
passage.
And brothers and sisters,
as you are listening,
I really want you to focus on
the words themselves, okay?
That is what is important right now.
Focus on the word.
That is right, Sister Ebony.
Amen.
Amen, Sister.
Now, let us focus on the second passage,
okay?
I am going to play the audio.
Throughout the universe, I am doing my
work.
And in the East, thunderous
crashes issue forth endlessly,
shaking all
denominations and sects.
It is my voice that has led all men into
the present.
I shall cause all men to be conquered by
my voice, to fall into this stream,
and submit before me.
For I have long since
reclaimed my glory from all the earth
and issued
it forth anew in the East.
Who does not long to see my glory?
Who does not anxiously await my return?
Who does not thirst for my reappearance?
Who does not pine for my loveliness?
Who would not come to the light?
Who would not look upon the richness,
of Canaan?
Who does not long for the return of the
Redeemer?
Who does not adore the Great Almighty?
My voice shall spread throughout the
earth.
I wish, facing my chosen people,
to speak more words to them.
Like the mighty thunders that
shake the mountains and rivers,
I speak my words to the
whole universe, and to mankind.
Hence the words in my mouth have become
man's treasure, and all men cherish my words.
The lightning flashes from the East all
the way to the West.
My words are such that man is loath to
give them up, and at the same time finds them unfathomable,
but rejoices in them
all the more.
Like a newborn infant, all men are glad
and joyful, celebrating my coming.
By means of my voice, I shall bring all
men before me.
Thenceforth, I shall
formally enter into the race of man.
so that they
will come to worship me.
With the glory that I radiate,
and the words in my mouth, I shall make it
such that all men come before me,
and see that the lightning flashes from
the East, and that I have also descended
unto the Mount of Olives of the East.
They will see that I have already
long been on earth,
no longer  as the son of the Jews, but
as the lightning of the East.
For I have long since been resurrected,
and have departed from mankind's midst,
and then reappeared with glory among men.
I am he who was worshipped countless ages
before now,
and I am also the infant forsaken by the Israelites countless ages
before now.
Moreover, I am the all-glorious,
almighty God of the present age.
Let all come before me, before my throne,
and see my glorious countenance,
hear my voice, and look upon my deeds.
This is the entirety of my will.
It is the end and the climax of my plan,
as well as the purpose of my management.
Let every nation worship me, every tongue
acknowledge me, every man repose his faith in me.
and every people be subject unto
me.
Amen.
All right, one more, okay?
One more, brothers and sisters.
Powerful passages, ain't it?
One more, okay?
And then we can ponder, we can reflect,
and we can share.
Everybody got it?
All right, let's listen.
As I turn my face to the universe to
speak, all mankind hears my voice,
and thereupon sees all the works I have
wrought throughout the universe.
Those who go contrary to my will,
that is to say, who oppose me with the
deeds of man, will fall down under my
chastisement.
I will take the multitudinous stars in the
heavens and make them anew.
And thanks to me, the sun and the moon
will be renewed.
The skies will no longer be as they were.
The myriad things on the earth will be
renewed.
All will become complete through my words.
The many nations within the universe will
be partitioned afresh and replaced by my nation
so that the
nations upon the earth will disappear forever
and become
a nation that worships me.
All the nations of the earth will be
destroyed and will cease to exist.
Of the human beings
within the universe,
all those belonging to the
devil will be exterminated.
All who worship Satan will be laid low by
my burning fire.
That is, except for those now within the
stream, the rest will be turned to ashes.
When I chastise the many peoples,
those in the religious world will,
in differing degrees, return to my
kingdom, conquered by my works,
because they will have seen the advent of
the Holy One riding on a white cloud.
All of humanity will follow
their own kind
and will receive chastisements varying
with what they have done.
Those who have stood against me will all
perish.
As for those whose deeds on the earth have
not involved me, they will,
because of how they have acquitted
themselves, continue to exist on the earth
under the governance
of my sons and my people.
I will reveal myself to the myriad peoples
and the myriad nations,
sounding forth with my own voice upon the earth to
proclaim the completion of my great work
for all mankind to see with their own
eyes.
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Thanks be to God.
We just listened to three powerful
passages from the sealed book.
Now, I got three questions.
Do you feel these words are full of
authority and power?
Does it feel like God is speaking to us
face to face?
Do you feel a sense of
awe in your heart when you hear these words,
brothers and sisters?
Yeah, how do you feel when you hear these
words?
Sister Shannon says, yes, I do.
Me too, my dear sister.
You know, I remember when I first heard
these words, I actually cried.
I said, oh my gosh, God is like warning me
in a sense.
I feel like I was being warned by God.
It's exactly how I felt too, sister.
Yeah.
Amen.
Maureen also feels like that.
Ronnie, Alberta, Rosita.
Warren says, no one else talks like that.
Exactly.
That's the whole point, Warren.
That's the whole point, my dear brother.
No one.
Except for God himself.
Which brings me to my next question.
Who could speak these words?
When you quiet your heart, when you focus
on these words word for word, do you think
A, only God can speak these words,
this is the voice of God?
Or B, oh, any man can say these things.
Or C, I'm not even sure.
What do you think, brothers and sisters?
Do you know how to tell
the difference between the word of your creator
compared to the word of men?
Do you know how to tell the difference?
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Very powerful passages, isn't it?
You see, all of you said, yeah,
this is the word of God.
Ebony, Shannon, Angela,
Maria, Clifton, Burr, Warren,
Jason, Dracos, Pamela,
Sophia, Maureen, Alberta.
Me too.
For six years, I've been knowing that this
is the word of God.
You see, brothers and sisters?
Because think about it, right?
Other than God, who can speak to all of
humanity?
Other than God, who can express and relay
to mankind God's intentions to save us?
Other than God, who can determine people's
outcome?
Who can control human life and death?
Who can control the stars in the universe
and hold sovereignty over all things?
Other than God, who can
publicly reveal the plans
and arrangements of
God's work in the last days?
As well as mankind's outcome and
destination ahead of time?
Other than God, who can
publicly announce God's administrative decrees
to the entire universe?
That's right, Sister Alberta.
Other than God, no one can do this.
You see, when you read these passages of
Almighty God's words,
it really allows us to see the authority, the power in the
word of God.
Like God had enough, brothers and sisters.
It's enough.
Mankind just keeps committing wickedness
in this world.
And God has had enough.
This is now time to perfect his people.
This is now time to express the truth so
mankind can turn from their evil ways.
You see, Almighty God's words is a direct
expression of God.
It is the voice of God.
You could see the Almighty God and the
Lord Jesus, brothers and sisters,
they share the exact same tone and manner
of speaking.
Both are expressions of God's disposition.
And this completely manifests God's
identity and essence.
It is only God incarnate who can speak to
mankind from the highest place.
Right?
This is revealing God's holy essence.
So when God's sheep hear Almighty God's
words like we did right now,
even if they don't understand the truth within them,
even if we don't even have much experience
of these words right
now, but you still feel
that every word carries
authority and power.
And because of this, you can be certain it
is the voice of God,
which perfectly fulfills what the Lord Jesus said,
brothers and sisters.
My sheep hear my voice.
And I know them and they follow me.
So the fact that you can identify the word
of Almighty God from the sealed book to be
the word of God, it goes to show,
brothers and sisters, without a doubt,
you are God's sheep.
And did you notice what God was also
telling us in these words?
He says, I am the Savior returned.
I am the Almighty God who conquers all of
mankind.
Rather, I am the God
who has returned in the last days and the God that
shall bring the age to an end.
What is God doing here, brothers and
sisters?
What is he saying?
He's literally telling us that he has
returned, brothers and sisters.
Yeah.
God himself is telling us.
He's here.
He has come back for a second time.
The Lord whom we've been waiting for day
and night, he is here.
And his name is Almighty God.
Because why?
He's come to conquer.
Just like I remember Brother Warren said,
it suits him.
I remember what you said last night,
Brother Warren.
The name Almighty God suits what God is
doing today.
You see?
And brothers and sisters, I hope you're
all paying attention.
Because I'm not just telling you that the
God has returned.
But I'm also telling you he has expressed
the truth.
He has brought his words and expressed all
truth.
And let me tell you something.
These words were not
spoken by someone among
us who has received
a revelation from God.
They were not spoken directly from God's
spirit, by the way.
Brothers and sisters, they
were words spoken by God
personally, after he has become
flesh, after he came to earth.
He's here.
Because no human being can express like
this.
Only God can express the truth,
brothers and sisters.
All right?
Only God.
That's right, Jason.
2,000 years of yearning and waiting.
That's right, my dear brother.
It's finally here.
Wow.
Brother Warren, I'm sure people do that.
But in the end, only God knows,
right?
Only God knows how long there is.
Right?
Because remember, 1,000 years for God is
like what?
One day?
Or 5,000 years is like one day for God?
Right?
Only God knows.
Only God knows, brothers and sisters.
All right?
And also too, there's something that like
a lot of people say, well, Sister Thelma,
you say that the Lord has come back.
Isn't that his spirit being here with us?
Brothers and sisters, I'm not talking
about the spirit of God coming back.
The spirit of God never left to come back.
He's the alpha and the omega, the
beginning and the ending.
He has always been here.
There's no such a thing as the spirit
returning.
All right?
Because when I'm testifying to you right
now that the Lord Jesus has returned,
it means he has become flesh a second
time.
It means he has come to earth a second
A flesh and blood.
He's expressing many new words and doing
new work.
So through the words of this ordinary son
of man, people can gradually recognize
that, wow, these words really are the
truth.
And they come to the
realization that, yeah,
Almighty God really is
the returned Lord Jesus.
Amen.
Brothers and sisters, we're going to talk
a lot today.
All right?
So please just continue to pay attention
and listen wholeheartedly.
All right?
Let's not jump to conclusion just yet
because I'm not done yet.
Okay?
I'm not done sharing more things.
So please keep up with me a little bit.
All right?
So brothers and sisters, do you think
these three passages in the audio that we listened to,
do you think they came from
the Bible?
Or do you think those were God's new words
outside of the Bible?
What do you think?
A, those passages are from
the Bible because only the Bible records what the
Lord Jesus said in the past.
So these words are God's new words outside
of the Bible.
Or B, these words are from the Bible.
Sorry, I didn't say it correctly.
A, the Bible only records what the Lord
Jesus said in the past.
So this audio that we listened to are
God's words outside of the Bible.
My apologies, okay?
Okay, sometimes I get too
excited brothers and sisters,
or B these words are from
the Bible or C I'm not too sure.
Oh sister Ebony, look at you sister.
Amen my dear sis.
Amen Warren and Dracos.
Anyone else?
Where are these words coming from?
Does anyone remember?
Are they really in the Bible?
Can they be in the Bible?
Can they?
No, it can't, right?
Because if it was from the Bible,
it would say Matthew, Mark, Matthew,
Mark, Luke, and John,
because obviously Matthew, Mark, Luke, and John
has Jesus's words, right?
It would say chapter this, verse that.
But as you could see, those were straight,
just words, just flowing, right?
Just words flowing from like the throne of
God.
It was just, just coming out.
And yeah, sister Ebony is correct.
Warren is correct.
So Sophia Dracos is also correct.
Brothers and sisters, these words come
from the sealed book.
Y'all remember the sealed book,
right?
Let me share with you the passages
brothers and sisters.
All right.
Remember the sealed
book was prophesied in the
book of Revelation, as
well as the book of Daniel.
Now pay attention
because God did mention in the time of the end,
there will be a new book.
Now look, Revelation was written by
apostle John, right?
It was the vision that God gave him in the
island of Patmos.
And in his vision, look what he saw.
And I saw in the right hand of him that
sit on the throne, a book written within
and on the backside, sealed with seven
seals.
And I saw a strong angel
proclaiming with a loud voice, who is
worthy to open the book and
to lose the seven seals thereof.
And no man in heaven, nor
in earth, neither under the
earth was able to open the
book, neither to look thereon.
And I wept much because no man was found
worthy to read the book,
neither to look thereon.
and one of the elder said to me, weep not, behold the lion of the tribe of the Juda
the root of David has prevailed to open the book and to loose the seven seals thereof.
So in the book of Revelation, I'm just
going to pause there for a second.
In the book of
Revelation, brothers and sisters, it clearly says
that there is a book.
John saw a book in his vision, but that
book was sealed, meaning it was closed.
So he started to cry because 2,000 years
ago, when John seen this vision,
the book was sealed.
No one was able to see it.
So he started to weep, he started to cry.
But one of the elders said to him,
don't cry, weep not,
because the lion of the tribe of Judah, the root of David,
will prevail to open the book.
Brothers and sisters,
the lion of the tribe of
Judah, that is literally
the returned Lord Jesus.
Now let's continue with Daniel.
Now look what God said to Daniel.
He said, you, O Daniel,
shut up the words and
seal the book, even
to the time of the end.
Many shall run to and fro, and knowledge
shall be increased.
And he continues to say, and he said,
go your way, Daniel, for the words are
closed up and sealed till the time of the
end.
Many shall run to and fro, and knowledge
shall be...
Many shall run, sorry, many shall be
purified and made white and tried,
but the wicked shall do wickedly.
And none of the wicked shall understand,
but the wise shall understand.
Look at that, brothers and sisters.
Look, God said, there is a new book in the
time of the end.
There are more words in the time of the
end.
And look, pay attention to the key.
The key point is, once this book is
opened, knowledge shall be increased.
And once this book is opened, many shall
be purified.
Look at that, brothers and sisters.
So, is the seal book open?
Yeah.
Because the Lord is here.
The seal book is open because Jesus has
already come back.
That's why we have the privilege to reading
these new words, brothers and sisters.
Now, let's go a little bit deeper.
Now, do you think the little scroll only
contains those few passages?
Can anyone guess?
How many words Almighty God has already
expressed so far?
Who wants to take a wild guess?
How many words do you think God has
expressed in the last days so far?
if you were to guess.
Okay.
I can tell you too.
Let's do a comparison, brothers and
sisters.
All right?
Because actually, Almighty God has expressed
already more than 10 million of words.
More.
That's proof God is here on earth,
brothers and sisters.
Those few passages
that I shared with you, it's
only like 0.0005% of what
God has already spoken.
There's more.
Now, I want to do a comparison here.
Because a lot of people may not know what
millions of words amount to.
Look at the Bible.
Did you know that the Bible only
has... The entire Bible, by the way.
From Genesis to the book of Revelation.
Did you know that it only has around
800,000 words?
That's little.
It doesn't even hit a million.
But the words that God expresses today is
over 10 million.
You want to know what 10 million of words
is?
Get the Bible.
Get the Bible, at least 12 of them.
Get 12 Bibles and put them together.
That's how many words God has expressed
for this evening.
That's a lot, isn't it?
That's a lot.
And it fulfills what the Lord Jesus really
did say.
I have yet many things to say to you.
Brothers and sisters, he was not joking
when he said, I do got to tell you things.
He says, I have to guide you into all
truth.
This is the time to guide us into all
truth, brothers and sisters.
This is the time to focus on the truth and
that's it.
Nothing else should matter in our life
except for the truth.
You see, brothers and sisters?
Because why?
The truth sets you free.
Now, with these 10 million of words,
wow, God has revealed so many mysteries.
Some of the mysteries you already know
because you've been here for four days.
But there are more mysteries that we're
going to talk about in the next four days.
But I'll just give you an idea.
There's the mystery of God's 6,000 year
management plan.
That was our topic last night.
That was a good topic.
The mystery of God's name.
That was also our topic last night,
which was a very good topic.
The mystery of the work of judgment.
That was day two sermon.
The mystery of incarnation.
That's day five tomorrow.
How God creates a group of overcomers
before the disasters.
That's Saturday's sermon.
What kind of people God saves and what
kind of people he eliminates.
Who can enter the kingdom of heaven and
who cannot.
The future outcome and destination of
mankind.
How the kingdom of Christ is realized.
How Satan corrupts people.
How to resolve the problem of sin.
How to achieve true love for God and so
much more.
Brothers and sisters, these mysteries are
totally eye-opening.
I know when I read all
of these mysteries, boy oh
boy was I convinced that
my creator is finally here.
I was convinced, brothers and sisters.
Because why?
God's new words today not only tell us
what he has done in the past, but it also
reveals what he is doing right now as well
as what he will accomplish in the future.
Now you tell me, other than God,
who can share his management plan?
Who can reveal all of these mysteries of
the kingdom of heaven?
Who can tell us the path of casting off
sin?
That's only God.
That's only God, brothers and sisters.
Because now think, right?
Through the past few days of our
fellowship, do you feel like you have
heard many truths?
Truth you've never heard before?
Do you feel like your
knowledge of God and his work
has grown significantly
to your knowledge?
Yes or no?
What do you think, brothers and sisters?
It's only been four days, right?
Only four days, but do you feel like
you've been learning a lot?
Angela says, yup.
Warren says, yes.
Bert says, yes.
Draco says, yes.
Alberta says, yes.
Ebony says, yes.
Shannon says, mm-hmm.
Tawana says, yes.
That's right, brothers and sisters.
Yeah.
You're in the right place.
You really are.
Because when you go to
church, brothers and sisters,
I'm not trying to bash
any church right now, okay?
But when you go to
church, you're listening to the
same sermon over and
over and over and over again.
They're flipping from the Old Testament to
the New Testament, the Old Testament.
It's like, why are you going backwards
6,000 years ago?
Show us something new, right?
But look, you've only been in our
fellowship for what?
Four days.
And your knowledge has already increased.
That's the true fulfillment of what God
told Daniel.
God told Daniel, by you, O Daniel,
shut up the words and seal the book,
even to the time of the end.
He said, many shall run to and fro, and,
key word, knowledge shall be increased.
Look, knowledge shall be increased.
Your knowledge is increasing every single
day.
Now, it's only been four days.
Now, imagine how much you would gain in
four weeks, four months, or even four years.
You see, just like myself, I've been in
this fellowship for six years.
That's why I'm very thankful and grateful
that I can hold this online sermon.
I can share with you the mysteries of what
God is doing today.
It took me time, right?
It took me time.
I had to learn more and more and more.
I had to read Almighty God's words so that
I could share freely with all of you.
And one day, that will be you too,
brothers and sisters.
All right?
And guess what?
I know you probably want to get your hands
on the sealed book, don't you?
But I will tell you, on Sunday,
if you stay with me till Monday,
on Sunday, I will actually give you a copy
of the sealed book.
Okay?
So for anyone right now who is truly
seeking the true way, if you're yearning
and thirsty for God's
appearance, brothers and sisters,
I'll give
you the book for free.
Zero.
Not even a dot.
Not even a penny.
Because at the end of the day,
God's words are free.
It's not like what man does, right?
Pastors, they want to make a dollar out of
everything, don't they?
Not here, brothers and sisters.
Not here.
This is God's fellowship.
All right?
And you will get the sealed book for free.
Yes, Tawana, I will give you all of that.
I'll give you all of that.
Okay, my dear brothers and sisters?
Amen, brothers and sisters.
That's right.
And also, too, my dear
brothers and sisters,
I know that I'm sharing with you
the Lord has come back.
And I know what the Bible says,
that, oh, false Christ will appear.
You don't want to be led on the wrong
path.
So tomorrow, we're going to learn what is
a true Christ, how to know the true Christ.
All right?
We will learn how to discern a true Christ
from a false Christ.
Okay?
And I know you're probably thinking,
okay, God is here.
Well, where is he?
What country?
Well, guess what?
On Saturday, we'll be talking about that
topic.
Okay, brothers and sisters?
So just please be patient with me,
okay?
Be patient with me.
If I gave you all at once, you would be
confused.
So I have to go step by step so you can
digest it slowly, slowly.
Okay, brothers and sisters?
All right?
So these words that Almighty God is
expressing today, it's abundant.
It's enough for us who
are God's sheep to really
welcome the Lord's
return in the last days.
Okay?
These over 10 millions of words?
That's enough proof  to know that your
Creator is here.
Because imagine not accepting...
Right?
Imagine not accepting, brothers and
sisters.
And then it comes to the
point where God is finally, you know,
he's finally giving
everyone the evaluation.
And you're going to say, well,
no one told me you're here.
I didn't know you were here.
But then he's going to say, well,
I put you in the fellowship.
I let you listen to my words.
Did you accept it?
Well, you're going to say, well, no, I
didn't accept it because I didn't believe.
Well, then he's going
to say, okay, you didn't believe, so you don't
believe in me, right?
You don't believe in my words.
Because remember, brothers and sisters,
believing in God is believing in his words.
Because God is his words.
You can't separate them.
Being face-to-face with God is being
face-to-face with the word of God.
All right?
Remember that, brothers and sisters.
So, with that being said, let's read more
words.
I feel like I'm talking too much.
I feel like I'm talking too much,
my dear brothers and sisters.
So, would you like to listen to more
passages of God's words right now?
Is that okay?
Can I play more audios of God's words?
Okay, yes, let's do that because I feel
like I'm running out of breath.
All right, so let's listen to another
passage of God's words, brothers and sisters.
And this is a passage of how God
determines people's outcome.
All right, it's not about,
oh, I go to church every
Sunday, oh, I read every
day, I pray every day.
No, it's not about that.
But listen, how does God determine our
outcome?
Almighty God says, Now is the time I
determine the ending for each person,
not the stage at which I began to work
man.
I write down in my record book one by one
the words and actions of each person,
as well as their path in following me,
their inherent characteristics,
and their final performance.
In this way no manner of
man shall escape my hand,
and all shall be with
their own kind as I assign.
I decide the destination of each person,
not on the basis of age, seniority,
amount of suffering, and least of all,
the degree to which
they invite pity,
but according to whether
they possess the truth.
There is no other choice but this.
You must realize that all those who do not
follow the will of God will be punished.
This is an immutable fact.
Therefore, all those who are punished are
so punished for the righteousness of God,
and as retribution for their numerous evil
acts.
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Look at that.
This passage, God is
telling us, now is the time
that He is determining
people's outcome.
And you can tell, right?
You can tell people are really being separated right
now, brothers and sisters.
Those who love the truth are with those
who love the truth.
Those who don't love the truth are those
who don't love the truth.
It's actually happening.
So who can determine our outcome?
Only God.
The words we just have read, it really
shows God's authority and power.
It's not something that I can express.
No pastor can express them.
No famous person,
your government, a great man
a religious leader,
no one can say that.
These words are entirely the Creator's
utterances to mankind.
God is showing us.
Right now is the time He is determining
people's outcome.
Amen.
Let's listen to another one, okay?
Another one.
I'll wait till everybody gets it.
All right.
The kingdom is expanding in humanity's
midst.
It is forming in humanity's midst.
It is standing up in humanity's midst.
There is no force that can destroy my
kingdom.
Of my people who are in
the kingdom of today, which
of you is not a human
being among human beings?
Which of you lies outside the human
condition?
When my new starting point is announced to
the multitude, how will humanity react?
You have seen with your own eyes the state
of mankind.
Surely, you do not still harbor hopes of
enduring forever in this world.
I am now walking abroad in the midst of my
people.
I live in the midst of my people.
Today, those who bear genuine love toward
me, people like these are blessed.
Blessed are those who submit to me.
They will surely stay in my kingdom.
Blessed are those who know me.
They will surely wield power in my
kingdom.
Blessed are those who seek after me.
They will surely escape from Satan's bonds
and enjoy blessing in me.
Blessed are those who are able to forsake
themselves.
They will surely enter into my possession,
and inherit my kingdom's bounty.
Those who run around for my sake,
I will commemorate.
Those who go to expense for my sake,
I will joyfully embrace.
Those who make offering to me,
I will give enjoyments.
Those who find enjoyment in my words,
I will bless.
They will surely be the pillars that hold
up the ridgepole in my kingdom.
They will surely have matchless bounty in
my house, and no one can compare with them.
Have you ever accepted the blessings that
you were given?
Have you ever sought the promises that you
were made?
You will surely, under the
guidance of my light,
break through the stranglehold
of the forces of darkness.
You will surely not, in the midst of
darkness, lose the light guiding you.
You will surely be the master of all
creation.
You will surely be an overcomer before
Satan.
You will surely, at the downfall of the
kingdom of the great red dragon,
stand up, amid the myriad throngs,
to bear witness to my victory.
You will surely be resolute and unwavering
in the land of Sinim.
Through the sufferings you endure,
you will inherit the blessing that comes from me,
and will surely irradiate all
within the universe with my glory.
Wow, brothers and sisters!
Makes you think, eh?
I live in God, who has the
authority and the power to make such promises to mankind,
and who can reveal mysteries.
Like what kind of blessings different types
of people will inherit in God's kingdom?
You see, only God can make these types of
promises, right brothers and sisters?
You could really see the mystery of God's
6,000 year management plan.
It's revealed to mankind.
Telling people truth and mysteries of the
purpose of of his managing of mankind.
The three steps, the depths of God's work
that we talked about yesterday,
the work that God is doing, the mystery of
incarnation.
Brothers and sisters, you really want to
know the mysteries of the bible?
God reveals it today as well in the seal
book.
Oh yeah.
He also reveals the outcome of each
people, the future destination of each
people, and how God
ultimately concludes the age,
and how his kingdom
is realized here on earth.
God also exposes the truth of how we have
been corrupted by Satan.
And all this, he does it through his work
of judgment.
Amen brothers and sisters.
Brothers and sisters, everyone clear so
far?
You still here with me?
Let me know in the chat box below.
All right.
Amen.
If you're still here, then let's continue,
okay?
Let's continue everybody.
Amen.
So brothers and sisters, does anyone
remember what is the work the Lord has come back to do?
What's the work the Lord has come back to
do, brothers and sisters?
He's already here, and what work is he
doing?
Hmm.
That's right, Dracos.
That's right, Warren.
That's right, Bert.
That's right, brothers and sisters.
It is the work of judgment, of
purification.
The Lord has returned, and the work of
judgment has begun.
Yeah.
Prophecies of the Lord's return regarding
his judgment, it's already here.
So through reading and accepting
Almighty God's words,
many people are already going through
the judgment and chastisement.
Brothers and sisters,
there are millions of people who have already
accepted the Lord's return.
Their corruptions are gradually undergoing
transformation.
Oh yeah, brothers and sisters,
God's work has already begun.
Yeah.
And they already, they're already
experiencing his judgment.
They have testimonies of being cleansed of
their sins.
And many of these brothers and sisters,
they share testimony of breaking free from jealousy,
breaking free from being a
dishonest person.
There's also testimony of breaking free of
arrogance and so on.
You name it.
You name it, brothers and sisters.
It fulfills, fulfills God's words in the
Bible.
God told Daniel, but you, oh Daniel,
but go your way, Daniel, for the words are
closed up and sealed to the time of the
end.
Many shall be purified and may white and
try, but the wicked shall do wickedly.
And none of the wicked shall understand,
but the wise shall understand.
Brothers and sisters, do you see?
Do you see?
Many shall be purified and may white.
So God knew that in the
time of the end,
He pertains to perfect, to
purify a group of overcomers.
That has already been fulfilled.
Now you may be asking, how do we prove that
the work of judgment has already begun?
Right?
How do we prove?
Brothers and sisters, it's the
testimonies.
Yeah, God's work of judgment has already
borne fruit.
And in the next upcoming
days, we will get to watch
some of the brothers and
sisters' testimonies, okay?
We'll start to watch testimonies from
Saturday.
Yeah, from Saturday we'll watch some
testimonies of our brothers and sisters
who have already accepted the Lord's
return.
But, nonetheless, I actually want to share
another passage of God's words, okay?
Brothers and sisters, when
you are listening to this passage of Almighty God's
words,
Please do not think of anyone else but yourself.
Alright?
Because a lot of people, they tend to read
the word of God and they will say,
oh, that's my uncle,
that's my sister,
that's how my uncle acts,
that's how my sister acts.
But no, think it for yourself.
Right?
Because God's word should target our own
corruption.
So listen here carefully.
Almighty God says, So many believe in me,
only that I might heal them.
So many believe in me,
only that I might use my
powers to drive unclean
spirits out from their bodies.
And so many believe in me, simply that
they might receive peace and joy for me.
So many believe in me, only to demand from
me greater material wealth.
So many believe in me,
just to spend this life in peace
and to be safe and
sound in the world to come.
So many believe in me,
to avoid the suffering of hell
and to receive
the blessings of heaven.
So many believe in me,
only for temporary comfort,
yet do not seek to gain
anything in the world to come.
When I brought down my fury
upon man,
and seized all the joy and peace he once
possessed, man became doubtful.
When I gave unto man the
suffering of hell,
and reclaimed the blessings of heaven,
Man's shame turned into anger.
When a man asked me to heal him, I paid
him no heed and felt abhorrence toward him.
Man departed from me to instead seek the
way of evil medicine and sorcery.
When I took away all
that man had demanded from me,
everyone
disappeared without a trace.
Thus, I say that man has faith in me
because I give too much grace,
and there is far too much to gain.
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Don't you feel like God was literally
exposing us?
Right?
When you read these words, brothers and
sisters, don't you feel exposed?
Yeah, that's deep, isn't it, Brother
Dracos?
Because I'll tell you how exactly I feel
when I read this passage of God's words.
You see, many people, they believe in God,
not because they truly know God.
It's because they want
something from God, whether
people want healing or
blessing or peace or protection.
But let me tell you, when God allows
difficulties and hardships to happen in our life,
when he removes
the blessings, or when God
does not meet our
expectations, what do people do?
They turn away from him.
Now, doesn't this
show you that people's faith in God is not build on the truth.
It's actualy build on personal gain.
So what is God's reminding us with this passage of words?
God is reminding us that
belief, true belief in God,
it's not about using God
for comfort, for benefits.
It's about seeking to know him,
following his will, pursuing the truth.
Because brothers and sisters, our creator,
he wants a relationship with us that is
based on love and obedience, not on
selfish desire.
All right?
So let us reflect here for a moment,
okay brothers and sisters?
I want us to reflect here for a moment.
You do not have to put your answer.
You can keep this answer between you and
God.
Just 10 seconds.
Answer this question between you and God.
Keep it in your heart.
You don't have to type it.
But I do want to ask you, why do you
believe in God?
Now really, just really think just between
you and God right now.
Are you seeking his heart?
Or are you the type of person that seeks
his hand, blessing, grace?
Do this for me, God.
Do that for me, God.
And I will believe in you longer.
Amen, brothers and sisters?
All right.
Thanks be to God.
You don't have to answer your question.
You don't have to answer this question,
okay?
Just between you and God.
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Thanks be to God.
So let's continue moving forward,
okay?
So every time I share that the Lord has
already come back, you know what people say?
They say, Sister Thelma, doesn't the Bible
say, but of that day and hour knows no man?
Not the angels of heaven, nor the son but my father only?
But why are you saying now that the Lord has already returned?
So how do you know?
Now, brothers and sisters, for someone
like me who has been spreading the gospel
for six years, yeah, it's going
to be six years in November,
I've come across a lot of
questions, and this is one of them.
All right, and I want to
explain to you, now that God is here.
it's about seeking the
truth wholeheartedly, okay?
So what does this verse mean, right?
This verse right now, of that day and hour
knows no man, that is referring to the
exact moment of God's arrival in the
flesh.
That's right, brothers and sisters,
no one knows when God became flesh again.
No one knows the exact moment,
the day, nobody knows.
But once Christ has come, once he began
performing his ministry, once he began
expressing the truth, of course,
people gradually will begin to recognize
his identity from his words and from the
utterances from his mouth.
That's just how it is.
So actually, okay, Sister Ebony,
no worries.
Actually, brothers and sisters,
when God becomes flesh for a second time,
no one
knows the days of his arrival.
No one welcomes him.
He simply just becomes flesh silently and
in silence.
You see, one day, he begins to express the truth.
and even then people will not recognize
him immediately.
But later, as he expresses more and more
and more words, flowing continuously like
living water, that's when people
suddenly realize and recognize
that he is the Lord Jesus
that has returned in the flesh.
So after he begins to
perform his ministry, to speak into work.
His words and his words gradually become
known to people.
And then more and more
people recognize that,
wow, yeah, he's the
Lord that has come back.
More and more people begin to testify to
the whole world that the Lord has returned.
So the fact that even
myself right now,
I'm letting you know that
the Lord has come back.
It does not mean that I knew this from the
very beginning.
I didn't.
I told you, I only knew this six years
ago, brothers and sisters.
It also does not mean that everyone can
hear God's voice.
All at the same time.
So when the first group of people
recognize the Lord Jesus by hearing his voice
they share the good news and they
testify about him to more and more people.
This is literally fulfilling the prophecy
in the book of Matthew.
And at midnight, there
was a cry made, Behold,
the bridegroom comes,
go you out to meet him.
That's the true fulfillment right there,
brothers and sisters.
All right.
Of that day and hour knows no
and that midnight, by
the way, brothers and sisters, midnight, it's
not referring to 12 a.m.
Midnight, it's literally referring to dark
times, wicked times on earth.
And isn't this the time that we're living
in right now?
Wouldn't you agree, brothers and sisters?
Are we living in dark hours, wicked times?
Yeah, we are.
We really are, brothers and sisters.
So now it's time.
Telling us and that midnight during wicked
time, evil time, a cry is made.
A cry, meaning people are going to preach
the gospel, that the bridegroom has come.
That's the return of the Lord Jesus.
Go you out to meet him, meaning come read
his words.
Come seek the truth.
All right.
So the true meaning of no one knows, it
means no one knows the exact day or hour.
Of the Lord's arrival.
I don't know when he was born, just
like nobody knows when Jesus was born.
And you can't tell me it was in December
because the Bible doesn't mention it.
Why? Because God does not want us to worship an
image.
God does not want us to worship a date.
God doesn't want us to sing happy birthday
to Jesus.
No, that's not what God wants.
God wants us to seek the truth.
Hence why God never told
mankind when he was going to come back,
but after the Lord comes,
people come to know him.
By his words and his work.
All right, brothers and sisters,
that makes sense, right?
And another thing too, a
lot of people may say, well,
sister Telma, tell me, how come I
never knew about this before?
Well, I could tell you the same thing.
How come I never knew this 10 years ago?
That's because brothers and sisters,
remember God returns as a thief in secret.
Meaning not everyone can hear this great
news at the same time.
God has really predestined the right time
for everyone to hear the good news of his return.
So today, this happens to be
the time that God has predestined
for you to hear the good
news of the Lord's return.
And let me tell you, you're not alone in
hearing this great news.
You're just one among millions.
Let me tell you in your country,
even in your hometown, there are so many
people there already that have already
accepted the Lord's return.
We just don't shout it at the top of our
lungs saying, Hey, God has come back.
No, there's wisdom in this brothers and
sisters.
You see the widespread of almighty God's
gospel in the last days really
does confirm in our hearts
that he's not an ordinary man.
He is the returned Lord Jesus.
It is just as we read in almighty God's
words.
Almighty God says my utterances shall be
propagated throughout the earth
and I shall utter and speak more
words to my chosen people
like mighty thunder, shaking
the mountains and river.
I speak my words to the whole universe and
to mankind.
Hence the words.
For my mouth has become man's treasure and
all people cherish my words.
You see how God always focuses on the
word.
It's always the word.
He didn't say, come follow me.
Come walk with me.
He says the word, he shifts us back into
the word.
Do you see that brothers and
sisters, because what God says
will be done and what he
ordains shall be accomplished.
So now that these words have already been
fulfilled.
The Lord, Jesus has returned in the flesh.
He's almighty God.
The truth is being expressed for this
instance.
And the work of judgment has begun.
The age of grace has concluded.
The age of kingdom has
now been ushered in
and the gospel of the
kingdom of heaven is here.
Remember what Jesus said 2000 years ago,
repent for the kingdom of heaven is at hand.
Well, guess what? Brothers and sisters.
he's brought it.
It's here.
Wow.
And you want to know the beauty of it too.
Today, God's words has already been
translated in over 40 languages.
That's a lot.
Not only that, but the gospel of almighty
God has spread to at least 120 countries,
including United States, Canada,
Ukraine, France, Germany, Italy,
Spain, South Korea, the Philippines,
you name it.
I can't even name 120 countries,
but it has already reached 120 countries.
We're going to watch a video on what day
on Sunday,
and I'll show you the many countries that have already accepted the
Lord's return.
Okay.
I'll show you some
videos and pictures as well,
brothers and sisters,
but it's quite amazing.
We, you know, us just being here in
fellowship, we are attending the wedding
feast of the lamb,
brothers and sisters,
you are protected by God
when you're in fellowship.
Yeah.
God is face to face with us in the age of
kingdom.
All right.
So I do want to ask all of you this.
Now, I want you to give me your sincere
answer.
Okay.
Now, let's read the question carefully.
The question is, now
that the little scroll has
been opened and the
work of judgment has begun.
Do you think?
The Lord Jesus has returned option a,
no, I don't think he has returned.
God inspired someone to write down these
words or B no, but he is returning soon
or C yes, he has come back, but in the spirit
or D yes, he has already come back on earth in the flesh a second time and has
personally spoken these new words.
What do you think brothers and sisters?
What do you think?
Rosita Pamela Tawana Alberta,
sister moreen Maria Yanis.
Tommy Dracos, Rani Warren, Shemaine,
Deborah, Jason Shannon, David,
and Eddie Clifton and Debra and pinky and
Janet, my dear brother Burt, Keisha
Chelsea Terry, Essie
What do you think, brothers and sisters?
Amen.
Amen. What about others?
Amen. Amen.
Amen. Brother Michael.
Amen. Angela.
Shannon, Dracos, and Warren.
Amen. Tawana, Alberta. Lily, amen.
Clifton, amen.
Maureen, amen.
So brothers and sisters, the correct
answer is D.
D is the correct answer.
That's right, Sister Maria.
Amen, Sister Angela.
That's right, brothers and sisters,
the correct answer is D.
Now, if you said C, I see your vision.
But remember, we cannot say the Spirit of
God has come back.
The Spirit never left.
Isn't that right?
The Spirit has always been here.
It's what leads and guides us.
Ain't that right, brothers and sisters?
Oh, that's okay, Sister Shannon.
Yeah, the Spirit of God never left.
It was here in the beginning.
It's still here, and it's going to be here
when we leave.
That will never change.
But when we say the
Lord has come back,
we are talking about God in
the flesh, the Son of Man.
Now, for my brothers and sisters who can
truly accept that the Lord has come back,
tomorrow, I'm going to put you all in a
group.
Okay, for those who can
accept the Lord is here,
I'm going to put you
all in a group together.
And I'm going to go deeper into the truth
with all of you.
I'll continue to share mysteries with you.
And yes, I will share the sealed book with
you.
Okay, that way, you can start reading
God's new words as well.
But let's continue.
Let's continue, brothers and sisters.
Okay.
So let me tell you something, Brother
Yanis, I see you said, B, what was B?
B, he will return soon.
So I want to share something with you,
Brother Yanis.
Okay.
When it comes to
welcoming the Lord's return,
it's not based on what
we see with our eyes.
It's not based on whether all the whole
world will accept it.
We got to be certain that the Lord has
already come back.
Because why?
You can hear his voice within the word of
Almighty God.
Because remember, only God can express the
truth.
Only God can open the sealed book.
Only God can begin the work of judgment.
So yes, the Lord has already come back.
Because why?
The truth is right in front of us.
Okay, Brother Yanis, and any brothers and
sisters as well.
All right.
Amen.
So now, let's talk about some,
some other things, brothers and sisters.
Okay.
Because you know, now that we share that
the Lord has already come back.
Oh, no worries, Brother Yanis.
My pleasure, my dear brother.
Now that we know that the Lord has already
come back, you know what people say?
Why haven't I not seen it on TV?
People say, why isn't it on the news?
Why?
Why don't the pastors and priests teach us
this in the churches?
Oh, brothers and sisters, let's consider a
question.
Okay, let me go step by step before I
attack all those questions at the same time.
Do you think that
after
hearing the good news that the Lord has
returned in the flesh?
DO you think everyone be willing to seek and
investigate God's new words and welcome Him?
What do you think brothers and sisters?
You guys are God's sheep.
You think everyone will be able to welcome
Him?
You think everyone is gonna wanna seek the
truth and investigate God's new words?
Brother Draco, you're... you're right.
What about others?
What do you think Shannon?
Yannis?
What do you think?
Exactly brother Michael?
No.
No, absolutely not.
You see, today people don't have a seeking
heart.
And let me tell you, brothers and sisters,
when it comes to the Lord's return,
people are not all happy.
Look what the Lord Jesus prophesied long
ago.
He literally said, For as the lightning
that lightens out of one part under heaven
shines to the other part under heaven,
so shall also the Son of Man be in his day.
But first must he suffer many things and
be rejected of this generation.
Look, have you thought about it?
Why will the Lord be rejected by our
generation when he comes back in the last days?
And look, the Lord Jesus still continues
to give us an answer as to why he rejected.
He literally said, this is an evil
generation.
You see that, brothers and sisters?
This is an evil generation.
And we live in an evil generation.
The Lord also says light is
coming to the world and men loved
darkness rather than light
because their deeds were evil.
The whole world lies in wickedness.
Do you see it?
Do you see it, brothers and sisters?
The true way has always been persecuted.
We live in an evil world.
Mankind has been deeply corrupted by
Satan.
Since ancient times, the
true way has always met with
opposition from this wicked
world and corrupt mankind.
So obviously in the last
days, this mankind has
been even more deeply
corrupted than before.
So of course God's work
in the last days is bound to
face resistance and condemnation
from this wicked world.
So obviously not everyone will welcome the
arrival of the Lord Jesus.
And that's a fact.
Now, based on this fact, let me ask you
another question.
Can welcoming the Lord today be based on
social media or news report?
Do you think social media is going to tell
you the Lord has come back?
Like TikTok, Instagram, the X,
Twitter?
Do you think it's going to tell you?
Once again, brother Dracos, you're right.
No.
Absolutely not.
No, no, no.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
No, obviously not.
The source of social
media or news report,
you've got to understand
where it comes from.
This wicked generation.
They come from man.
They reflect the
viewpoints of man, the
prejudices of man, and
even the schemes of Satan.
Not the truth.
Even many media outlets, they claim to be
impartial.
They may resist and condemn the return of the Lord Jesus
And Satan loves to use the media to mislead
people's hearts with all kinds of lies.
Brothers and sisters, the media does
nothing but lie.
Exactly, brother Warren.
Many would think it's a joke.
That's so true, my dear brother.
It's manipulation.
That's right, brother Dracos.
It's so true, brothers and sisters.
You see, this perfectly
fulfills the prophecy the Lord
did say that he will be
rejected by our generation.
So you can obviously see, right,
that social media and the news report,
they don't come from God.
They cannot be used as a basis for
investigating the true way.
You see, throughout history, mankind could
not accept the true way.
Right?
Those among mankind who
could accept the true way and
follow the true God has always
been a very small minority.
You see, not the whole world.
The whole world does not love the truth.
Only a minority do.
The vast majority of people, they just
love to follow the trends of the world.
They love to seek and investigate.
They don't love to seek and investigate
the true way.
They love to follow the trends of the
world.
Look how many trends are happening in this
People just go along with it.
So ultimately, these are the people that
lose their chance of salvation.
That's exactly what the Bible says.
It is mentioned in the Bible.
Right?
Jesus said, enter you in at the straight
gate.
Look, look, there's two sides.
One, for wide is the gate, and broad is
the way that leads to destruction.
And many there be which go in their act.
Now, what about the other way?
Because straight is the gate, and narrow
is the way that leads to life,
and few there be that find it.
You see, brothers and sisters, many are
called, but only few will find the true way.
So when it comes to welcoming
the Lord's return, right, you
cannot look whether the
majority of people have accepted.
Who cares if the whole world is rejecting
it?
Follow God, brothers and sisters.
All right?
You need to look at whether this son of
man, almighty God, can express the truth
and can do the work of saving people.
Because the only path
to investigating the true way
is to focus
on hearing God's voice.
That's it.
That's it, brothers and sisters.
Focus on the truth.
All right?
Amen.
That's one key point.
Now, another thing that people
are saying... is asking their pastor.
You see, when I share the great news,
people say, I have to go ask my pastor,
and elder, because my pastor understands
the Bible.
If the Lord has returned,
he would definitely
appear to the pastor
and tell them first.
And if the pastor believes the Lord has
returned, I will believe it too.
But if my pastor does not believe it,
neither will I.
Brothers and sisters, do you agree with this viewpoint?
Alberta says not true.
Michael says nope, I don't agree.
Burt says nope.
Warren says nope.
Brothers and sisters, quite frankly, I don't agree either.
To be honest with you.
Yeah, me too, sister Maria.
I don't at all.
Alright? because you really need to really think.
That is okay, sister Tawanda.
You need to think what kind of people are pastor and elders.
Do pastors and elders represent God?
No, they cannot.
Do they have the truth?
No, they do not.
Do they understand the truth?
No, they don't.
So why must the Lord, right?
Why must the Lord reveal himself to the
pastors and elders when he comes?
Did the Lord say that?
Brothers and sisters, is there any Bible
verse that says, when the Lord comes back,
it will be the pastor that will know
first?
Is there any Bible verse that says that?
That's right.
No, there isn't.
Alberta says they're just like us.
They are, sister.
They're wicked and corrupted, just like
us.
They're no better than us.
You see, even 2,000 years
ago, when the Lord Jesus came
to do his work, what kind
of people did he look for?
Did he look for the pastors?
Did he look for the Pharisees and the
chief priests?
Did he notify them in the temple?
Did he notify them in the synagogues?
No, he didn't.
The first one he chose was an ordinary
person.
Brothers and sisters,
the very first person that Jesus actually chose
to follow him was who?
Simon Peter.
It was Simon Bergona.
He literally said, Simon Bergona,
will you follow me?
Who was Simon?
He was a fisherman.
He was a regular person just like us.
Isn't that right?
Because that's the thing with God.
He's not looking at how high or low
someone's status is, nor does he look at
who understands the Bible better,
who has biblical knowledge.
God is not looking at that.
He's not looking at that at all.
Brothers and sisters,
God is looking at those
who seek humbly and
whoever can accept the truth.
So now look at your pastor.
Have you ever really examined your pastor
thoroughly?
Would you say that he's someone who
accepts the truth?
Would you say he's someone that God
approves of?
Can he represent God?
Do you know these things?
You gotta know these things.
He cannot represent God, right?
If he cannot represent God
and if he is not someone God
approves of, why do you entrust
your final destination to him?
Why do you entrust your salvation to your
pastor?
Is that not human ignorance and
foolishness?
Is that not being a foolish virgin?
Think about another question.
Two thousand years ago.
Who was the main culprit who nailed the Lord Jesus to the cross?
Does anyone know brothers and sisters?
who is the main culprit who nailed the Lord Jesus
to the cross?
Once again, it was the pastors.
It was literally the religious world.
Yeah, it was the
Pharisees, brothers and sisters.
because it wasn't
the Roman government.
Because who told the Roman government to
crucify Jesus?
It was the Pharisees, the religious
leaders, who were well-versed in the Bible.
They were waiting for the Messiah.
Yeah, but they didn't accept the Messiah.
They didn't accept the Lord Jesus.
That's right, youngies.
They took the lead in resisting and
condemning him instead.
You see, brothers and
sisters, that should really,
really, really make
you think, shouldn't it?
They were stubborn.
They were arrogant.
They were old-fashioned.
They spent years explaining
the Bible to people in the
synagogues, and they were all
waiting for the Messiah to come.
But when the Lord Jesus appeared and
worked, even though they clearly knew the
Lord's words had authority and power, the
Pharisees did not seek or investigate it.
They even blocked believers
from accepting the true way,
and they ultimately nailed
the Lord Jesus to the cross.
Do you want to know why?
They were jealous of Jesus.
They knew that Jesus had many followers,
and everybody else was leaving.
Because remember, brothers and sisters,
Jesus, when he began his ministry,
he never preached inside of the synagogue
or the temple.
He preached outside by the water, by
the boat, on the mountains, on the stream.
He was gaining a lot of followers.
Meaning, a lot of people were leaving
the churches back then,
they were leaving the synagogues and
the temple just to follow Jesus.
Thousands of people!
They were jealous, right?
And not only that, even more.
They thought that the Messiah was going to
be born in a palace.
They thought the Messiah was going to be
rich.
But when they saw When they had seen that
Jesus was born in an ordinary family,
had no status, it was very hard for them
to accept him.
So they delimited God within their own
notions and imagining.
They delimited him within the letters of
the Bible.
And that's the mistake that a lot of
people do today.
You see, the Pharisees, they were clinging
to the name of the Messiah.
And no matter how many truths the Lord
Jesus expressed, no matter how much
authority and power his words had,
they still refused to seek and accept him.
So the root cause of the Pharisees'
resistance, like you see, they were
arrogant, they were stubborn, they were
old-fashioned.
They lacked God-fearing heart.
They did not seek the truth at all.
And that is why they were capable of
nailing the Lord to the cross,
committing a heinous crime, and suffering
from God's punishment.
Now that God has become flesh again,
history is repeating itself.
What is the attitude of our pastors today?
You see, the entire religious world,
who are they waiting for it to come?
They're waiting for the
Messiah, sorry, they're waiting
for the second coming of
Christ to come on a white cloud.
But when pastors and elders hear,
when we testify that God is actually
already here in the flesh to express the
truth, same thing as the Pharisees.
They don't want to seek, they don't want
to investigate.
Because why?
It's different from their own ideas.
Because it's different from what they
learned in theology.
So what do they do?
They jump to conclusion and they
automatically say it's false.
But have they ever listened to a sermon?
Have they ever read passages of Almighty
God's words?
No, they haven't.
You see, regarding this
amazing matter of the
Lord's return, they
just jump to conclusion.
They don't investigate the true way at
all.
People don't investigate the true way
anymore.
So it's clear.
They're also arrogant.
They lack a God-fearing heart.
They don't seek the truth at all.
They are also walking the exact same path
as the Pharisees.
Now, if you let your pastors and elders
act as the gatekeeper of the gate,
and when it comes to welcoming
the Lord's return,
are you also not going to be led
astray, brothers and sisters?
Are you also not going to be down on the
wrong path of resisting God?
Don't you have a mind of your own to seek
the true way?
You see, after hearing the
good news of the Lord's return,
people don't know how to
discern for themselves anymore.
Nor do they come before God to pray and
seek.
They don't allow God to guide them
anymore.
Instead, they just want to
believe what pastors say, because,
oh, pastors are the ones
that preach in the churches.
But brothers and sisters, look what the
church is becoming today.
Go deeper.
You see, a lot of people claim to believe
in God, but they depend on pastors.
It's sad.
People want to follow their pastors.
They let the pastors control everything.
They think, oh, my pastor has authority.
The pastor is greater than God.
The pastor's words are greater than God's.
Brothers and sisters,
when you really think about it,
these people don't
believe in God at all.
They believe in their pastors.
And what did Peter teach us?
We ought to obey God.
Rather than men.
Isn't that right?
We ought to obey God rather than men,
brothers and sisters.
You see, this is the
behavior of a foolish virgin
who does not
listen to the word of God.
They're nothing but foolish.
Ignorant.
Just like the Jewish people back then.
They blindly worship and follow the
religious leaders.
As a result, they become people who
actually resist God and suffer God's
punishment.
Actually, every person's destiny is held
in the hand of God.
It's not held in the hand of a pastor.
So regarding the great matter of the
Lord's return, as believing in God,
welcoming the Lord, and attaining
salvation, you should never, you should
never ever entrust your life to the hands
of a pastor.
Much let your pastor
decide for you whether
you should welcome
the Lord's return or not.
Because, brothers and sisters,
if you let them decide, then you are
actually being very irresponsible with
your own destination.
So when investigating the true way,
you need to have a mind of your own.
You absolutely cannot be constrained by
anyone.
The most crucial factor
in welcoming the Lord
is whether a person can
recognize God's voice.
All of us are in a spiritual battle.
But you've got to focus the word of the
truth.
Okay?
If you want to be a wise virgin,
you've got to read the word of God.
You've got to recognize the word of God.
You've got to know that the word of God is
the true way.
Only such people are unbound and
unconstrained by anyone.
Only they can follow resolutely.
All right, brothers and sisters.
So when it comes to investigating the true
way, we have to read God's words.
On the other hand, a foolish virgin?
Oh, they hope for the Lord to descend on a
white cloud.
And even though
Almighty God has already expressed millions of
words, they turn a deaf ear.
They don't see.
They don't investigate.
They're really stubborn.
They just judge and condemn.
And people like this,
brothers and sisters, by their nature,
they're not
destined to hear God's voice.
They're not destined to welcome the Lord.
These people are nothing but tares.
They're nothing but wicked ones that
eventually will be revealed by God's work.
And you'll know who these people are.
They will be abandoned, eliminated,
and punished by God.
Brothers and sisters, let us listen to the
final passage for tonight.
Final passage for tonight.
What are the consequences of not accepting
the true way?
By the way, this passage is very long,
but it's so good.
And I want you to listen to every single
word that God is saying right now.
Okay?
Let's listen.
Many people may not care what I say,
but I still want to tell every so-called saint,
who follows Jesus that, when you see
Jesus descend from the heaven upon a white
cloud with your own
eyes,
this will be the public appearance of
the sun of righteousness.
Perhaps that will be a time of great
excitement for you.
Yet you should know that the time when you
witness Jesus descend from the heaven
is also the time when you go down to hell to
be punished.
It will herald the end of God's
management plan.
And will be when God rewards the good and
punishes the wicked.
For the judgment of God
will have ended before man sees signs.
when there is
only the expression of truth.
Those who accept the truth and do not seek
signs, and thus have been purified,
shall have returned before the throne of
God and entered the Creator's embrace.
Only those who persist in the belief that
the Jesus who does not ride upon a white
cloud is a false Christ shall be subjected
to everlasting punishment.
For they only believe in the Jesus who
exhibits signs, but do not acknowledge the
Jesus who proclaims severe judgment and
releases the true way of life.
And so it can only be
that Jesus deals with
them when he openly
returns upon a white cloud.
They are too stubborn, too confident in
themselves, too arrogant.
How could such degenerates be rewarded by
Jesus?
The return of Jesus
is a great salvation for
those who are capable
of accepting the truth.
But for those who are unable to accept the
truth, it is a sign of condemnation.
You should choose your
own path and should not
blaspheme against the Holy
Spirit and reject the truth.
You should not be an ignorant and arrogant
person, but someone who obeys the guidance
of the Holy Spirit and longs for and seeks
the truth.
Only in this way will you benefit.
I advise you to tread the path of belief
in God with care.
Do not jump to conclusions.
What's more, do not be casual and carefree
in your belief in God.
You should know that, at
the very least, those who
believe in God should
be humble and reverential.
Those who have heard
the truth and yet
turn their nose up at it are
foolish and ignorant.
Those who have heard the
truth and yet carelessly jump
to conclusions or condemn
it are beset by arrogance.
No one who believes in Jesus is qualified
to curse or condemn others.
You should all be someone who is rational
and accepts the truth.
Perhaps, having heard the way of truth and
read the word of life, you believe that
only one in ten thousand
of these words are
in line with your
convictions and the Bible.
And then you should continue to seek in
that ten thousandth of these words.
I still advise you to
be humble, to not be
overconfident, and to not
exalt yourself too highly.
With your heart holding such meager reverence
for God, you will gain greater light.
If you carefully examine and repeatedly
contemplate these words,
you shall understand whether or not they are the
truth and whether or not they are life.
Perhaps, having only read a few sentences,
some people will blindly condemn these
words, saying, this is nothing more than
some enlightenment of the Holy Spirit,
or this is a false Christ come to deceive
people.
Those who say such things are blinded by
ignorance.
You understand too little of the work and
wisdom of God.
And I advise you to start again from
scratch.
You must not blindly condemn the words
expressed by God because of the appearance
of false Christs during the last days,
and must not be someone who blasphemes
against the Holy Spirit because you fear
deception.
Would that not be a great pity?
If, after much examination, you still
believe that these words are not the truth.
are not the way, and are not the
expression of God,
then you shall ultimately be punished and be without
blessings.
If you cannot accept such
truth spoken so plainly and so clearly,
then are you
not unfit for God's salvation?
Are you not someone who is not fortunate
enough to return before the throne of God?
Think about it.
Do not be rash and impetuous, and do not
treat belief in God as a game.
Think for the sake of your destination,
for the sake of your prospects,
for the sake of your life, and do not play
around with yourself.
Can you accept these words?
Wow.
That was a lot, right, brothers and
sisters?
Can you accept these words?
You see, brothers and sisters,
as we're coming down to the end,
I really, you know, I really hope that we
will all take this to heart.
Because think about it.
Haven't we been hoping for the Lord to
come our entire life?
And today, within our
lifetime, the Lord has
come at a time where
we least expected it.
This is the most important thing in our life.
And it involves our outcome and our
destination.
So I really hope that you will treat this
matter seriously and cautiously.
Don't jump to conclusion.
Or don't even give up investigating the
true way, okay?
Perhaps, yeah, you have doubts.
Perhaps you have questions that we haven't
obviously completely answered them yet.
But that's very normal, okay?
That's normal.
Because the process of investigating the
true way itself is a process, right?
It takes time, brothers and sisters.
What, you think I knew everything all in
one day?
I'm still learning.
It's six years and I'm still learning,
brothers and sisters.
Alright?
So it's really a process
of gradually resolving
doubts and correcting
notions and concerns.
It's just as Almighty God says.
Do not be rash and impetuous.
And do not treat belief in God as a game.
Think for the sake of your destination,
for the sake of your prospect,
for the sake of your life, and do not play
around with yourself.
So when it comes to hearing the good news
that the Lord has come back, yeah,
this is the most crucial moment for us to
seek the truth.
So choose correctly.
It will be an eternal regret when you
choose wrong.
Right?
So no matter how much confusion we have,
I really hope that you'll continue to
participate and finish the next four days.
Okay, brothers and sisters?
Because as long as you have
a seeking heart, you know
you will find the answers
within the Word of God.
And another thing I want to tell you guys
before you guys go is that, okay,
today we heard the good news of the Lord's
return.
And I know many of you
are probably eager to tell this good news.
to the people around
you that God has come back.
But let me tell you something,
brothers and sisters.
It's not wise to tell
people
that God has already come back
because you're just starting.
You're just starting.
All right?
And you cannot explain it clearly to them.
Because if you tell other people,
people directly that the Lord has come back.
not only will they not
accept the good news,
but it's also going to hinder them
from gaining God's salvation.
I don't know if you've seen this before,
but even 2,000 years ago,
the Lord Jesus warned His disciples it wasn't time to
tell people about Him.
Right?
It wasn't time.
Jesus warned His disciples that they
should tell no man of Him.
Why?
Because around that time, people had a lot
of imagination about God.
Right?
They were not able to understand the truth
at that point.
You see, brothers and sisters?
So God asked them, don't tell anyone that
He was the Messiah.
Instead, He continued to teach them the
truth.
Right?
Because or else, people would judge and
oppose.
People would sin with their mouth and
condemn God.
If you do that, that's like losing your
salvation.
So what do we need to do?
We need to study first.
Okay?
Wait for the right time, brothers and
sisters.
Okay?
Wait until you actually understand more
truth.
Wait until you can actually testify to the
Lord's return.
Then you can share with them.
Or you can just invite them to join our
gathering.
Let them learn step by step like you did.
Instead of just directly telling them that
the Lord has come back.
Okay?
So brothers and sisters, I do have a
review question.
Like I said, tomorrow I'm making a new
group.
So right now, how many groups do we have?
We have 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8 groups.
Right now we have 8 groups.
But tomorrow, I want to make one group.
And that depends on your answer.
Brothers and sisters, do you believe the
Lord has already returned?
Or do you feel He will return soon?
How do you feel?
He has already come back?
Or will He return soon?
Amen, Dracos.
You can feel free to share.
Okay, brothers and sisters?
Yeah, feel free to share.
Pamela, Tawana, Alberta, my dear sister
Maureen, Maria, Yanis, Tommy, Shemaine,
Debra, Foylene, Lily,
David, Eddie, Clifton, Debra,
Janet, what do you
think, brothers and sisters?
Can you accept that the Lord has already
come back?
Amen.
Amen, Alberta, Tawana, Dracos, Warren,
Shannon, Michael, Maureen, Bert, Lily.
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
All right.
So brothers and sisters, all of you that
said yes, He is here.
Tomorrow, we get to go to a new group.
Okay?
Amen, Brother Clifton.
We get to go to a new group.
So this group that you're in right now is
not going to be called.
No one's going to call this group anymore.
We are going to go to a new group
tomorrow.
Brother Yanis, what about your answer?
You can feel free to answer as well.
Okay, my dear brother?
That way, I know how to prepare your group
for tomorrow.
All right, my beloved brother.
Amen.
So yes, tomorrow, no one's going to call
this group anymore.
We are going to have a different group.
Those who can accept the Lord's return,
you will go to a new group.
Those who said, I need more time,
you can go to a different group.
And that's okay.
All right?
Those who need more time, you will have
another preacher.
All right?
You will have another preacher.
But for the brothers and
sisters who can accept the Lord has come back,
I will
continue to be your preacher.
I will continue to share more exciting new
topics with all of you.
Okay?
Yeah.
Four more days.
Okay?
I'm excited.
Because tomorrow
night, brothers and sisters,
we're going to talk
about the incarnation.
All right? Because, you know, I wish I could share
more with you.
But obviously, you know, there's two
hours.
It's already gone by.
And there's so much more
mysteries that I need to
share with you regarding
the Lord's second coming.
Like where does God appear this time?
When did he begin to express the truth?
What has God accomplished up until now?
So please do not be quick to give up.
Before you hear more.
There's more.
So no matter how many doubts
you have, I really hope that
you'll continue to join this
group and seek the truth.
Remember, seek and you shall find.
Okay, brothers and sisters.
And I know some of you may also be
concerned.
Oh, false Christ, false prophets.
We're going to talk about that.
Don't be scared of false Christ and false
prophets.
False Christ and false prophets,
they can do nothing to you.
All right, brothers and sisters,
they cannot do nothing to you.
But regarding that, this topic,
we'll talk about tomorrow.
All right, you'll gain more of an
understanding.
What does a false Christ do?
What does a true Christ do?
All right, brothers and sisters.
So I hope you'll come back tomorrow.
You'll continue to learn more truth.
And I will add you into the new group.
Okay?
Let's do a quick prayer before we go.
Let's all pray before we go.
Okay, brothers and sisters.
I'm sorry I took you for two hours and 20
minutes.
Okay?
So let's pray here together.
Amen.
Dear almighty God, Father God, we thank
you so much for such an incredible topic.
Thank you for finally revealing yourself
to us within your words, dear God.
I think many of us
here tonight, we had a
feeling that you were
already here, dear God.
But we just didn't know how to execute our
feelings with that.
So we thank you.
Thank you for knocking at the door of our
hearts.
Thank you for revealing yourself to us,
dear God.
Now it's up to us.
Now we have to do the work.
It's by joining more
fellowship, reading more of your words.
fellowshipping together
as your sheep, dear God.
As you can see, we all come
from different places, different
backgrounds, different
religion, different skin color.
But the only thing that actually
continuously brings us together is you.
It's your work.
It's your truth, dear God.
This is how we're all united.
Now imagine how the whole world, if the
whole world could be like this, dear God.
But we know the whole world rejects you.
But while you're here, dear God,
we pray.
We pray that you could do everything you
can to lead and to guide us.
We know you're not doing the work of signs
and wonders.
You're doing the work of expressing the
truth.
Because it is only the truth that will
help us realize that we lack.
We lack so much, dear God.
But nonetheless, you're here.
You're here to save us.
You're here to express the truth that is
needed for our salvation.
So we just want to thank you wholeheartedly.
For your love, for your support, and everything that
you do in our lives, dear God.
And I pray for all my brothers and sisters
who are here as well.
I know they're going through their own
difficulties in their life.
But I pray that you be with them,
dear God.
You lead them and you guide them.
Show them that we're not here alone.
So we thank you.
We thank you for all that you do.
And we just want to give
you all the praise, all the honor,
and all the glory in your
precious, righteous, holy name.
Dear God, we pray.
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Thanks be to God.
My beloved brothers and sisters,
thank you so much for your time.
All right.
I really do appreciate it.
Like I said, I'm so sorry I took a while.
I'll definitely give you a call.
I sent you a message privately,
everybody, okay?
Check your other groups, okay,
brothers and sisters?
I sent you guys all a message.
So you can feel free to answer that
message.
And I'll give you guys a call tomorrow.
But if you want me to call you tonight,
I can call you tonight.
Like Brother Draco, I would love to call
you tonight.
All right.
And also Sister Shannon, Michael,
Jason, if I could call you tonight,
that would be amazing.
Okay?
So you can just let me know in the chat
box if it's okay.
I can call you tonight.
I know Brother Warren says for me to call
him tomorrow at 5 p.m.
So I will definitely do that, Brother
Warren.
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
All right.
Praise be to God.
All right, brothers and sisters,
I'll see you soon, okay?
I'll see you very soon, everybody.
May God bless you.
May God bless you, everyone.
Thanks be to God, Brother Yanis.
Thanks be to God.
All right, Brother Dracos, I'll call you
right now, then, okay?
Okay, Sister Shannon.
Okay, Sister Tawana.
No problem.
All right, Brother Michael.
All right.
Blessings on to you, okay, everyone?
God bless.